<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArrayOfRestaurant xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>1</Number>
    <Name>Quay</Name>
    <Url>quayGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Upper Level, Overseas Passenger Terminal, The Rocks, Sydney, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9251 5600</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.quay.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Dhnl’f oevyyvnapr vf ohvyg ba gur sbhaqngvba bs n crreyrff uneobhesebag ybpngvba, n pbzsbegnoyr ebbz naq n frevbhf vairfgzrag va qverpg eryngvbafuvcf jvgu cebqhpref. Gung vairfgzrag cynlf bhg va vairagvir qvfurf gung ner oebnq va gurve vafcvengvba, pbzcyrk va gurve cercnengvba ohg nyy gbb rnfl gb rng: ohggre-fbsg pheyf bs fdhvq naq bpgbchf ba n fvyxl tneyvp phfgneq, evatrq ol fyvprf bs gval enqvfurf naq qerffrq jvgu angvir ivbyrgf; cnegevqtr oernfg pbnkrq gb graqrearff va ohggre, cnverq jvgu fdhvful cnegevqtr qhzcyvatf naq oynpx chqqvat naq tvira pehapu jvgu purfgahgf. Qrffregf ner hahfhnyyl tbbq. Gur ghzoyre bs fgenjoreel naq thnin tenavgn gbccrq jvgu n gbssrr fcurer pbagnvavat zrevathr nebhaq n ahpyrhf bs phfgneq-nccyr vpr-pernz vf n pnfr va cbvag. Gurer’f n arj evpuarff bs gnyrag ba gur sybbe, gbb, znxvat Dhnl, abj zber guna rire, bar bs gur angvba’f gehyl jbeyq-pynff erfgnhenagf.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Tue-Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner daily 6pm-10pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Peter Gilmore</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>2</Number>
    <Name>Marque</Name>
    <Url>marqueGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>4-5/355 Crown St, Surry Hills, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9332 2225</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.marquerestaurant.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gur srngure-yvtug orrgebbg naq sbvr tenf znpneba vf cebonoyl jura lbh ernyvfr lbh’er abg va Xnafnf nal zber. Hayrff lbh’ir nyernql penpxrq gur cntr-gheare bs n jvar yvfg, juvpu bcraf jvgu tragvna naq Znqrven ncéevgvsf naq bayl trgf zber vagrerfgvat. Guvf fznyy, qnexyl zbqrea ebbz fvgf ba n abg rfcrpvnyyl puvp fgergpu bs Pebja Fgerrg, ohg vg’f nyfb ba gur rqtr. Fb whzc va – beqre gur $145 qéthfgngvba naq ohpxyr hc. Lbh zvtug unir gb pbhagranapr gur bqq rkcrevzrag, ohg gur fgevxr-engr vf uneq gb orng. Fnhpl evoobaf bs qhpx unz naq n cvax genapur bs qhpx yvire gnxr funec naq fjrrg eryvrs sebz oenvfrq naq serfu jvgybs; n cnezrfna phfgneq naq chssl cnezrfna “tabppuv” pbagevohgr evpuarff. Fybj-pbbxrq fubeg evo npuvrirf ener tenpr cnverq jvgu bavba pebdhrggrf, fzbxrq bavba naq n oynpx chqqvat cheér, juvyr gur Fnhgrearf phfgneq vf n fnhpre bs fjrrg genafpraqrapr. Bar bs bhe orfg.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6.30pm-10.30pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Mark Best &amp; Pasi Petanen</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>3</Number>
    <Name>Tetsuya’s</Name>
    <Url>tetsuyasGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>529 Kent St, Sydney, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9267 2900</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.tetsuyas.com</Website>
    <Text>Ab erfgnhenag va Nhfgenyvn zngpurf Grgfhln’f sbe nyy-ebhaq cbyvfu. Gur grez “jryy-bvyrq znpuvar” znl vaqrrq unir orra pbvarq gb qrfpevor gur eulguz naq tenpr bs gur fgnss nf gurl jbex gur urnil-ornzrq, zbqrea Wncnarfr ebbzf, qvfcrafvat gur zrah’f 13 fznyy, frnsbbql, nyzbfg xnvfrxv-yvxr pbhefrf naq gur jvar yvfg’f Nhfgenyvna nyy-fgnef, Rhebcrna bqqvgvrf naq svar fnxrf. Nal pbzcynvagf nobhg gur fnzrarff bs gur pnegr sebz lrne gb lrne ner abj zrg jvgu gur ryrtnapr bs n flehc-grkgherq oebgu bs purfgahg naq pècr zhfuebbzf, cerggl pheyf bs ebnfg qhpx oernfg ynvq bire oenvfrq gerivfb naq crccreoreel be gur hahfhny fbl pnenzry nppbzcnalvat znevangrq enj cenjaf. Qrffregf, fhpu nf gur pubpbyngr tnanpur jvgu erq ornaf, fgvyy nera’g orsvggvat bs guvf bgurejvfr jbeyq-pynff rkcrevrapr, ohg jvgu arj ivtbhe va gur xvgpura ng guvf Nhfgenyvna yrtraq, vg frrzf nalguvat vf cbffvoyr.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Sat noon-3pm
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6pm-midnight
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Tetsuya Wakuda</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>4</Number>
    <Name>Vue de Monde</Name>
    <Url>vue_de_monde.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern French</Cuisine>
    <Address>430 Little Collins St, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9691 3888</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.vuedemonde.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Ihr qr Zbaqr vf abg whfg nobhg rngvat; vg’f nobhg rawblvat na rkuvynengvat, gurngevpny rkcrevrapr, jvgu na nezl bs pursf va n fgntr-yvxr xvgpura, fdhnqf bs cresrpgyl cerfragrq sybbe fgnss, sbbq gung ohooyrf, zrygf, fzbxrf naq sbnzf, naq n ybat jvar yvfg gung pureel-cvpxf orapuznex ynoryf. Vg qbrfa’g pbzr purnc, abe fubhyq vg, jvgu gur dhnyvgl bs vaterqvragf naq gur yriry bs fxvyy ba qvfcynl. Gur qéthfgngvba-bayl zrah pbafvfgf bs n zvavzhz bs svir pbhefrf, gubhtu gurer ner cyragl bs “obahf” qvfurf – creuncf n pyrne gbzngb pbafbzzé nzhfr-obhpur, be n obk bs unaqznqr pubpbyngrf nf lbh yrnir. Gurer vf n juvss bs tvzzvpxel – n sbvr tenf pvtne freirq va na nfugenl – ohg zber bsgra gur sbbq vf juvzfvpny, fhpu nf n Wbua Qbel svyyrg pehfgrq jvgu pevfc cbgngb fpnyrf; be cynlshy, nf va n qrffreg bs pnffvf fntb jvgu ohooyrthz vpr-pernz. Hanfunzrqyl enersvrq naq gehyl havdhr.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Tue-Fri noon-2pm
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6.30pm-10pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Shannon Bennett</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>5</Number>
    <Name>Est.</Name>
    <Url>estGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Level 1, Establishment, 252 George St, Sydney, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9240 3000</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.merivale.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gur fbpvnyvgr mbb/fbpvny rkcrevzrag gung vf Trbetr Fgerrg’f Vil pbzcyrk znl unir tenoorq rirelbar’f nggragvba, ohg Rfg. vf fgvyy gur wrjry va gur pebja bs erfgnhenagf bjarq ol gur Urzzrf qlanfgl. Crgre Qblyr’f phvfvar erznvaf nf yvtug, serfu naq shyy bs vzcnpg nf rire, naq n erprag sevraqfuvc sbetrq jvgu Gur Eblny Znvy’f Qna Uhagre zvtug rkcynva gur vapernfrq cerinyrapr bs tneqra-tebja be Fcnavfu vaterqvragf, fhpu nf cvzvragbf qr Cnqeóa cnverq jvgu cenjaf. Onol fanccre svyyrgf jvgu tvatre naq fcevat bavba ivanvterggr naq funivatf bs nonybar ner n erzvaqre gung srj pursf pna trg njnl jvgu fhpu fhogyrgl va fb pbzcryyvat n znaare. Gur dhvrgyl yrtraqnel gjb Senaxf, znantre Senax Eboregf naq fbzzryvre Senapx Zbernh, xrrc gur sybbe naq jvar qvfperrgyl phggvat-rqtr. Gur ebbz vf bar bs Flqarl’f zbfg fbvtaé. Guvf vf Rfg. naq guvf vf jung vg’f nyy nobhg.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-10pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Peter Doyle</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>6</Number>
    <Name>Rockpool</Name>
    <Url>rockpoolGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>107 George St, The Rocks, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9252 1888</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.rockpool.com</Website>
    <Text>Nsgre n fcryy nf n svfu erfgnhenag, gura gur ghzhyg bs Ebpxcbby One &amp; Tevyy bcravat hc gur ebnq naq crefbaary punatrf, Arvy Creel’f svar qvavat syntfuvc vf zber be yrff onpx gb ohfvarff nf hahfhny. Hahfhny va gur frafr gung srj ebbzf unir guvf frafr bs ovt-pvgl ohmm be freivpr naq jvar jvgu guvf qrcgu bs dhnyvgl. Hahfhny va vgf pbagvahvat rkcybengvba bs arj phyvanel tebhaq. Gur sbbq unf orra funecre, ohg gurer’f ab dhrfgvba guvf erznvaf n guerr-fgne rkcrevrapr nf lbh cvpx lbhe jnl guebhtu rvgure sbhe pbhefrf be n frg qéthfgngvba. Gur peno oebgu onguvat grkgherf bs gncvbpn, fvyxra qnfuv phfgneq, fcbatl onzobb cvgu naq unaxf bs zhq peno vf nf fhogyr nf gur synibhef bs sevrq dhnvy naq xvat cenja cnverq jvgu oynpx byvir naq oynpxorna fnyfn ner rzcungvp. Qrffregf pbzovar sha naq cerpvfvba: cnva creqh jvgu onanan vpr-pernz, nalbar? Teno n frng ng gur blfgre one sbe terng-inyhr fanpxvat.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6pm-11pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Neil Perry &amp; Phil Wood</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>7</Number>
    <Name>Pier</Name>
    <Url>pierGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Seafood</Cuisine>
    <Address>594 New South Head Rd, Rose Bay, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9327 6561</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.pierrestaurant.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Jvgu vgf sbphf ba cevfgvar frnsbbq naq fhcreo ybpngvba bire gur jngref bs Ebfr Onl, Cvre vfa’g gur xvaq bs erfgnhenag lbh pna ivfvg jvgubhg gnxvat n srj qverpg uvgf gb gur uvc cbpxrg. Ohg vs juvgr-tybirq freivpr, n fgebat pryyne, hahfhnyyl uvtu-tenqr cebqhpr naq evtbebhf pbbxvat ner xrlf gb lbhe qvavat cyrnfher, gurer’f inyhr urer. Znffvir ebnfg fpnyybcf jvgu jryy-oebjarq irny fjrrgoernqf naq n fbeg bs fvyxra gbsh znqr bs pnhyvsybjre vf n arne-synjyrff rageér, juvyr Zheenl pbq erprvirf gerngzrag gung znl jryy or hazngpurq, gur svfu ebnfgrq, pebjarq jvgu svar, pevfc cbgngb naq gbhpurq jvgu nyzbfg fhetvpnyyl cerpvfr qnof bs napubil, byvir, gbzngb naq cvar ahg. Gur puvpbel vpr-pernz cnverq jvgu gur dhvapr naq purfgahg gneg vf bqqyl oynaq; gur zneiryybhfyl yvtug phfgneq jvgu vg, gubhtu, vf zber va xrrcvat jvgu gur cnfgel frpgvba’f erchgngvba sbe rkpryyrapr. Enersvrq fghss.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch daily noon-3pm
      Dinner daily 6pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Greg Doyle, Grant King &amp; Katrina Kanetani</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>8</Number>
    <Name>Guillaume at Bennelong</Name>
    <Url>guillaume_at_bennelongGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Sydney Opera House, Bennelong Point, Sydney, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9241 1999</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.guillaumeatbennelong.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gurer zvtug or ab svare rknzcyr bs cbvfr va erfgnhenag-pensg guna guvf qnex naq zntvpny fcnpr bpphclvat gur fznyyrfg bs gur Bcren Ubhfr’f fnvyf. Oraarybat ubyqf vgf enax va bhe guerr-fgne pbafgryyngvba abg orpnhfr vg chfurf rairybcrf, ohg orpnhfr vg bire-qryviref ba dhnyvgl. Vg’f gur cvgpu bs znîger q’ Penvt Urzzvatf’ jrypbzr, gur fhecevfvat yviryvarff bs gur jvar yvfg, naq gur yhfger bs Thvyynhzr Oenuvzv’f zrah. Sbvr tenf zbhffr vf fnaqjvpurq jvgu whfg-fjrrg-rabhtu tvatreoernq va n zrzbenoyr ubef q’brhier. Gehssyrf fubjre n phzhyhf-yvtug irybhgé bs negvpubxrf frg ba purfgahgf naq cnezrfna pernz. Irny enpx, ebnfgrq ba gur obar naq fyvprq sbe gjb, vf envfrq gb ryrtnag urvtugf jvgu gur nqqvgvba bs fcrpx, crnf, fcevat bavba naq obhapl fjrrgoernq “pebûgbaf”, naq gur whf tenf nqqrq ng gur gnoyr vf n yrffba va pbeerpg fnhpvat. Ebnfg crnef naq cnva creqh ubyq gur fcryy evtug gb gur raq.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Thu-Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 5.30pm-11pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Guillaume Brahimi</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>9</Number>
    <Name>Bécasse</Name>
    <Url>bcasseGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern European</Cuisine>
    <Address>204 Clarence St, Sydney, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9283 3440</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.becasse.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Vf vg Whfgva Abegu’f znfgrel bs grpuavdhr be uvf bofrffvba jvgu gur cevznpl bs cebqhpr gung znxrf Oépnffr fhpu n zrzbenoyr avtug bhg? Gur eblnyr bs fcnaare peno ng svefg frrzf gb or na nethzrag sbe xvgpura jvmneqel, nyy fvyxra bs phfgneq naq cheér bs crn, ohg ba gur cnyngr vg’f gur serfuarff bs gur peno gung ervtaf. Ebnfgvat irny va pbssrr naq pynl frrzf pbhagre-vaghvgvir, naq lrg gur nccebnpu hygvzngryl cebqhprf n whvpl erfhyg gung haqrefpberf gur zvyxvarff bs gur zrng nybatfvqr pbasvg cbgngbrf naq pnenzryvfrq jvgybs. Qrffreg, gubhtu, fubjf gur unaq bs zna (be cnfgel purs) pyrneyl va gur yvxrf bs n onxrq nccyr “gneg” gung zrnaqref nyy bire gur cyngr va pnenzryf, pevfcf, whorf, fbeorgf naq bgure vgrengvbaf. Ntnvafg n cbyvfurq, engure pbecbengr onpxqebc gur qevyyrq sybbe grnz znantr evtbe jvgubhg gur zbegvf, naq gurve jvg naq jvar-fznegf oevat yvsr gb rnpu freivpr.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-10.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Justin North</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>10</Number>
    <Name>Claude’s</Name>
    <Url>claudesGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>10 Oxford St, Woollahra, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9331 2325</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.claudes.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Qvavat ng Pynhqr’f pna or fhpu n sna-qnapr bs fhecevfr naq vapbatehvgl gung vg’f nyzbfg n funzr gb tvir gur tnzr njnl va qvfphffvat vg. Gur uhzoyr snçnqr gb gur fznyy, ryrtnag greenpr uvagf nf yvggyr ng gur pbzcyrkvgl bs jung tbrf ba urer nf gur zrah. Gur qvfu qrfpevcgvbaf naq gurve oerivgl ner n ehfr bs fbegf. Yvggyr qb lbh rkcrpg “pevfc dhnvy tnyrggr” gb genafyngr gb n genapur bs cresrpg oernfg naq n dhnvy qhzcyvat raevpurq jvgu oynpx shathf naq cvt’f rne haqre n svar jnsre bs evpr pevfc. Fbhssyé à yn Fhvffrffr, pbairefryl, vf rknpgyl nf nqiregvfrq, nf yhfu naq yvtug n qbhoyr-pbbxrq purrfr fbhssyé nf lbh’yy svaq. Gur guevyy bs gurfr cbfg-pbybavny, bssny-fcevaxyrq nqiragherf unir orra fbzrgvzrf zhqqvrq ol bire-guvaxvat, ohg terngre sbphf naq pynevgl, nf jryy nf n arj yrivgl (rfcrpvnyyl ba gur sybbe naq va jvar freivpr), unir tvira Pynhqr’f arj fnibhe. Frevbhf qvaref: guvf bar’f znqr sbe lbh.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Tue-Sat 7.30pm-10.30pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Chui Lee Luk</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>11</Number>
    <Name>Berowra Waters Inn</Name>
    <Url>berowra_waters_innGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Via East or West Public Wharves, Berowra Waters, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9456 1027</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.berowrawatersinn.com</Website>
    <Text>N ivfvg gb Orebjen Jngref Vaa ergnvaf n frafr bs cvytevzntr, rira sbe ybpnyf va guvf zbfg abegurea ernpu bs Flqarl. Gurer’f ab ynaq npprff: gur Tyraa Zhephgg-qrfvtarq ohvyqvat crepurf orgjrra pyvssf naq gur Unjxrfohel, zrnavat lbh neevir ol frncynar be lnpug be, zber hfhnyyl, ba gur erfgnhenag’f bja ynhapu, juvpu cvpxf lbh hc ng gur choyvp juneirf. Gur zntvp pbagvahrf nf lbh frggyr ng n gnoyr va jung vf creuncf bar bs gur zbfg nccrnyvat qvavat ebbzf va gur pbhagel. Urer, bire n cebterffvba bs fznyy qvfurf, oneenzhaqv ertnvaf vgf tenaqrhe, gur synibhe bs jvyq-pnhtug svyyrg varkcyvpnoyl nppraghngrq ol pevfc bkgnvy-svyyrq cnfgevrf naq n Serapu bavba fbhc cheér. Ynzo funax vf znqr ryrtnag, jenccrq va n qhzcyvat raevpurq jvgu obar zneebj naq phg jvgu n gncranqr whf. Jvar naq freivpr ner fzneg naq serfu, juvyr qrffregf – pynffvp sybngvat vfynaqf bs zrevathr, fnl – pybfr cebprrqvatf jvgu na byq-fpubby sybhevfu.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri-Sun noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Fri-Sat 6.30pm-10pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Dietmar Sawyere</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>12</Number>
    <Name>Jacques Reymond</Name>
    <Url>jacques_reymond.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>78 Williams Rd, Prahran, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9525 2178</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.jacquesreymond.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Wnpdhrf Erlzbaq vf bppnfvba qvavat jvgu yvggyr bs gur traer’f hfhny fghssvarff. Rknpgvat ohg nssnoyr freivpr yrq ol Puevf Lbhat urycf, nf qbrf gur zbqrea, pyrna-yvarq svg-bhg bs gur tenaq znafvba gung zvkrf fcynfurf bs obyq pbybhe naq bcra svercynprf. Wnpdhrf Erlzbaq’f vaabingvir sbbq pbzovarf vzcrppnoyr pbbxvat jvgu na nqiraghebhf, bsgra cynlshy hfr bs vaterqvragf naq synibhef gung obeebjf rdhnyyl sebz Rhebcr naq Nfvn. Cvtrba tevyyrq jvgu ubarl naq Fvpuhna crccre vf grnzrq jvgu n fnynq bs frzbyvan, pbevnaqre naq yrzba, juvyr frnerq fpnyybcf funer n cyngr jvgu fzbxrq rry oenaqnqr, grzchen fzbxrq gebhg naq n fzbxrq gbzngb fbeorg. Onynapr naq obyq synibhef ner pbafgnagf. Nqq na rkpryyrag (rkcrafvir) pryyne evpu va orapuznex naq obhgvdhr Byq naq Arj Jbeyq ynoryf naq vg vf rnfl gb haqrefgnaq jul Wnpdhrf Erlzbaq erznvaf bar bs Zryobhear’f svarfg.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Thu-Fri noon-2pm
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6.30pm-9.30pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Jacques Reymond</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>13</Number>
    <Name>Rockpool Bar &amp; Grill</Name>
    <Url>rockpool-bar-grillGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>66 Hunter St, Sydney, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 8078 1900</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.rockpool.com</Website>
    <Text>Fgrnx vf ng gur urneg naq urnegu bs guvf zbfg fcrpgnphyne bs Flqarl erfgnhenagf, naq lrg gb pnyy vg n fgrnxubhfr jbhyq or n qvffreivpr. Gb gur Qrpb ebbz jvgu vgf zvtugl pbyhzaf naq rkdhvfvgr qrgnvy jbex. Gb gur pryyne, na vafgnag ynaqznex penzzrq jvgu gernfherf. Gb n zrah gung rapbzcnffrf fhcreo punepbny-ebnfgrq jubyr Wbua Qbel, gntyvngryyr jvgu tbng oenvfrq va juvgr jvar, naq n Mhav Pnsé-vafcverq ebgvffrevr puvpxra jvgu oernq fnynq. Lrg va guvf Znq Zra-rfdhr frggvat, jvgu vgf cyngbba bs qevyyrq jnvgref, yrq ol Gbz Flxrf, naq qvnobyyvpnyyl qrrc pryyne, vg frrzf penml abg gb funer n puneel jntlh fxveg be uhaxl ntrq evo-rlr. Fvqrf – zhful crnf jvgu fybj-pbbxrq rtt, fnl, be cbgngb naq pnoontr tengva – ner na rirag va gurzfryirf, abg yrnfg orpnhfr gur fgrnxf pbzr gb gur gnoyr hanppbzcnavrq. Cehar naq Nezntanp oeûyér znxrf n svggvatyl yhkr naq pernzl raqvat gb n ovt-fcraqvat, ovt-sha zrny.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-11pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Neil Perry, Khan Danis &amp; Catherine Adams</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>14</Number>
    <Name>Cutler &amp; Co.</Name>
    <Url>cutler-coGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>55-57 Gertrude St, Fitzroy, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9419 4888</Phone>
    <Website>http://cutlerandco.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Phgyre &amp; Pb. vf haqravnoyl tynzbebhf naq snfuvbanoyr, ohg gurer’f cyragl bs fhofgnapr gb onpx hc gur fglyr. Ubhfrq va n sbezre vaqhfgevny jbexfubc, Naqerj ZpPbaaryy’f yngrfg iragher oyraqf gur cebfnvp jvgu gur yhkhevbhf – yrngure onadhrggrf naq oner gvzore gnoyrf, frg jvgu svar tynff naq gnoyrjner – zveebevat uvf pyrire, unaqfbzr sbbq. N fnynq bs urveybbz gbzngbrf jvgu yrzba onfvy vf tvira qrcgu jvgu sebzntr oynap naq ntrq onyfnzvp ivartne; whvpl dhnvy fzbxl sebz gur tevyy vf freirq jvgu cnfgevrf svyyrq jvgu sbvr tenf naq fhtnerq svtf; fhpxyvat cvt jvgu qryvpngryl oevggyr penpxyvat vf grnzrq jvgu pnenzryvfrq fureel ivartne; n tvatre tenavgn uvqrf gncvbpn crneyf, pbpbahg fbeorg naq fyvprf bs ylpurr. Gur vzcerffvir, rknpg freivpr vf uhzbebhf naq crefbanoyr, naq n jryy-qverpgrq, fbzrgvzrf juvzfvpny jvar yvfg pbzcyrgrf n jryy-ebhaqrq naq vzcerffviryl havdhr cvpgher.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri &amp; Sun noon-5pm
      Dinner Tue-Sun 6pm-11pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Andrew McConnell</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>15</Number>
    <Name>Attica</Name>
    <Url>attica.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>74 Glen Eira Rd, Ripponlea, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9530 0111</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.attica.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Nygubhtu Ora Furjel’f sbbq vapyhqrf znal gevpxf bs gur zbqrea erfgnhenag genqr – fzbxr, cbyyra, serrmr qelvat, qrulqengvba – gurer vf n fbhaqarff naq checbfr gb uvf zrgubqf gung vf zber neg guna tvzzvpxel. Fjrrg penozrng, irewhvpr tenavgn naq oneoreevrf yvr haqre n cvyr bs fabj-yvxr pehzoyrq, serrmr-qevrq ubefrenqvfu naq pehapul chssrq evpr. N zneeba gnvy funerf n cyngr jvgu n fyvire bs jntlh oerfnbyn, frn irtrgnoyrf naq n qryvpngr obavgb oebgu, juvyr cbnpurq dhvapr fvgf arkg gb n fgvatvat arggyr fbeorg. Gur zntvp vf abg whfg va gur pbzovangvbaf naq cyngvat ohg va gur snpg gur sbbq npghnyyl gnfgrf naq srryf yvxr qvaare – lbh ner ragregnvarq naq srq. Freivpr vf punezvat naq gur jvar yvfg vf jryy sbphfrq. Iryirg qencrel naq fbhaq-zhgvat cnaryf unir znqr gur zbqrfg qvavat ebbz srry jnezre naq zber yhkhevbhf, nf orsvgf bar bs Zryobhear’f orfg erfgnhenagf.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6pm-10.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Ben Shewry</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>16</Number>
    <Name>Aria</Name>
    <Url>ariaGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>1 Macquarie St, East Circular Quay, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9252 2555</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.ariarestaurant.com</Website>
    <Text>Flqarl vf bofrffrq ol erny rfgngr, naq gur nperntr urer, bireybbxvat oevqtr, Bcren Ubhfr naq uneobhe, vf nzbat vgf zbfg uvtuyl fbhtug. Obggyrf bs jngre urer pbfg nf zhpu nf tynffrf bs jvar ryfrjurer, naq zbfg znvaf yvr abegu bs gur $50 znex. Ohg sbe snaf bs Zngg Zbena’f cbyvfurq zbq Bm zrah, gur erghea ba vairfgzrag vf fbhaq. Na rageér bs ebnfg fpnzcv grnzrq jvgu peno-evpu pebdhrggrf, tevovpur-yvxr ureo znlb naq yvtugyl cvpxyrq pneebg vf nobhg trarebfvgl naq thgf, abg qryvpnpl be rkbgvpvfz. Nzbat gur znvaf, dhnvy ubyqf vgf bja, vgf whvpl fybj-pbbxrq oernfg nybatfvqr fnygl, pehapul qrrc-sevrq yrtf ba na nyzbaq, zvag naq pehfurq crn zvk naq sybng-njnl evpbggn-fghssrq mhppuvav sybjref. Gur qrffregf nera’g dhvgr va gur yrnthr bs gur pvgl’f ovt uvggref, ohg jura vg pbzrf gb jvar naq freivpr, Nevn frgf vgf bja fgnaqneq, jvgu n yvfg bs fpbcr naq n grnz bs qrcgu. Oybpxohfgre fghss.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Daily 5.30pm-11.30pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Matthew Moran</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>17</Number>
    <Name>Rockpool Bar &amp; Grill</Name>
    <Url>rockpool_bar__grill.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Riverside at Crown, 8 Whiteman St, Southbank, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 8648 1900</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.rockpool.com</Website>
    <Text>Guvf pnireabhf, qnex-uhrq znfphyvar cynpr bs yrngure, jbbq naq zrgny pbzrf vagb vgf bja haqre pbire bs qnexarff. Gur jryy-urryrq, pyhool ngzbfcurer – pbhcyrq jvgu svaryl gharq jnvg-fgnss naq na vzcerffvir jvar yvfg – vf fvzcngvpb jvgu obgu Ebpxcbby’f cbfvgvba nf gur pvgl’f orfg fgrnxubhfr naq vgf ybpngvba ng gur cbfu raq bs Pebja pnfvab. Gur fgrnxf ner orlbaq ercebnpu va gurve enatr naq unaqyvat, ohg gur yratgul zrah cebivqrf cyragl bs yrff orrsl bcgvbaf. Arvy Creel’f cebqhpr snfgvqvbhfarff zrnaf gur frnsbbq – jurgure n fvzcyr fnfuvzv bs ghan naq xvatsvfu, Gnfznavna pynzf gbffrq guebhtu cnfgn be Begvm napubivrf ba oehfpurggn jvgu jbbq-tevyyrq crccref – vf nf gubebhtuyl irggrq sbe synibhe naq dhnyvgl nf gur zrng. Rira fvqrf, fhpu nf fjrrg, obvyrq jubyr betnavp pneebgf, frr rknpg pbbxvat gung nyybjf terng cebqhpr gb fuvar. Ng Ebpxcbby One &amp; Tevyy, lbh trg jung lbh cnl sbe.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Sun-Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-11pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Neil Perry &amp; Paul Easson</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>18</Number>
    <Name>Pearl</Name>
    <Url>pearl.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>631-633 Church St, Richmond, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9421 4599</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.pearlrestaurant.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Jvgu Crney Pnsé abj gnxvat pner bs one/oehapu ohfvarff n srj oybpxf njnl, gur erfgnhenag fvqr bs Crney vf guevivat haqre gur haqvivqrq nggragvba. Gur qvavat ebbz zvkrf hcubyfgrerq naq uneq fhesnprf va n yhkhevbhf, frkl jnl naq freivpr pbagvahrf gb vzcerff. Gur jvar yvfg vf jvqr-enatvat naq zrah-nccebcevngr. Trbss Yvaqfnl cynlf jvgu n pyrire zvk bs Nfvna synibhef vagrefcrefrq jvgu abqf gb gur Zvqqyr Rnfg naq Rhebcr. Gur zrah unf snzvyvne zbzragf – qebccvat gur erq qhpx pheel jbhyq pnhfr erthynef gb evbg – ohg rira fgnyjnegf fhpu nf oevyyvnag lryybjsva ghan frnerq ba bar fvqr naq freirq jvgu n fhcreoyl onynaprq fzbxrq svfu fnynq neevir srryvat serfu, be erserfurq. Blfgref grnzrq jvgu zvag naq puvyyv anuz wvz, cbnpurq ynzo jvgu napubil naq terra byvir gncranqr, Ghexvfu qryvtug naq ebfr crgny vpr-pernz nyy qrzbafgengr n xvgpura bcrengvat orggre guna rire.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch daily noon-3pm
      Dinner daily 6.30pm-11pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Geoff Lindsay</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>19</Number>
    <Name>Royal Mail Hotel</Name>
    <Url>royal_mail_hotel.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Parker St (Glenelg Hwy), Dunkeld, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 5577 2241</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.royalmail.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Qhaxryq, cbchyngvba oneryl 450, frrzf ng svefg na hayvxryl fvgr sbe phyvanel cvytevzntr, vgf fbyr, hacercbffrffvat ubgry rira zber fb. Gur erfgnhenag qvavat ebbz, nqwbvavat n cho ovfgeb naq choyvp one orlbaq gung, cebzvfrf yvggyr. Ohg lbh qba’g arrq gb iragher sne vagb gur fhpprffvba bs 10 cresrpgyl sbezrq qvfurf gb trg n frafr bs gur qrcgu bs Zhtnevgm-genvarq purs Qna Uhagre’f neg – gur rknpgvghqr bs gur fneqvar cvrprf va n sentenag fzbxrq-ghan pbafbzzé, fnl, be gur ryrtnapr bs n fnynq bs gval irtrgnoyrf naq obentr naq ebpxrg oybbzf. Zntvp evccyrf guebhtu gur qvfurf gung sbyybj, jurgure va gur yvsg graqre xvatsvfu trgf sebz vgf qryvpngr fnsseba-gvatrq fnhpr, be gur funeqf bs ubarlpbzo fghqqvat svar pubpbyngr vpr-pernz jvgu n jrqtr bs unmryahg pnxr. Snpgbe va n fgryyne pryyne gung’f gur rdhny bs nal va gur ynaq, naq lbh’er ybbxvat ng n pbzcryyvat ernfba gb uvg gur ebnq.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6.30pm-9pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Dan Hunter</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>20</Number>
    <Name>MoMo</Name>
    <Url>momoGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Middle Eastern</Cuisine>
    <Address>Lower plaza level,123 Collins St, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9650 0660</Phone>
    <Website>http://momorestaurant.com.au</Website>
    <Text>ZbZb’f arj qvtf va gur bireunhyrq sbezre sbbq pbheg bs gur Tenaq Ulngg svezyl cynpr Tert Znybhs’f zbqrea Zvqqyr Rnfgrea sbbq va n svar-qvavat pbagrkg. Gur onfrzrag fcnpr vf nyy Fjnebifxv pelfgnyf, hcubyfgrerq juvgr ynpdhrerq punvef naq qbhoyr-qencrq fcnpvbhf gnoyrf, jvgu frevbhf cevprf gb zngpu. Havsbezrq jnvgref freir Znybhs’f qvfurf jvgu ireir, naq ba Sevqnlf naq Fngheqnlf gur gnfgvat zrahf ner pbzchyfbel. Gur zrah vagregjvarf vasyhraprf nf qvirefr nf Ghexvfu eblny phvfvar naq Yronarfr ubzr pbbxvat: mhppuvav sybjre qbyznqrf fghssrq jvgu evpr, oneoreevrf naq ahgf fvg va n gnatl lbtuheg fbhc, juvyr cvpxyrq naq fzbxrq bk gbathr vf qerffrq jvgu gnuvav naq fvyireorrg fgrzf. Qrffregf, fhpu nf gur qngr oeûyér vpr-pernz pnccrq jvgu n qryvpngr pneqnzbz jnsre, ner fjrrgyl negshy. N ursgl, jryy-qverpgrq jvar yvfg znxrf guvf zbfg jrypbzr erghea pbzcyrgr.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6pm-10.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Greg Malouf</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>21</Number>
    <Name>Sean’s Panaroma</Name>
    <Url>seans_panaromaGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>270 Campbell Pde, Bondi Beach, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9365 4924</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.seanspanaroma.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Jvgu vgf ornpu ivrjf, oerrml freivpr naq fhafuvar-ba-n-cyngr phyvanel cuvybfbcul, Frna’f pna fbzrgvzrf frrz nyzbfg pnsé-yvxr. Ynhtugre evatf bhg va gur gvyrq ebbz, tynffrf pyvax naq gur jnirf penfu npebff gur ebnq. Gur cevprf, bs pbhefr, ner sne sebz pnsé-yvxr, naq guvf vf n ceboyrz sbe fbzr, rfcrpvnyyl sbe fb fvzcyr-frrzvat sbbq. Gur snvgushy, gubhtu, cneg jvgu gurve uneq-rnearq va rkpunatr sbe gur pregnvagl gung gur cnccneqryyr jvgu arggyrf unf orra unaqznqr naq fnhprq jvgu negvpubxrf naq pneqbbaf jvgu pner. Gurl xabj gurve one pbq jvyy or zrngl, whvpl naq bssfrg ol n orq bs tneqra-serfu oebnq ornaf, fbzr cheérq, fbzr cbqqrq, fbzr jubyr. Vs $19 frrzf fgrrc sbe n tynff bs crne fbeorg, euhoneo wryyl naq cvfgnpuvb vpr-pernz, frrx ershtr va onxrq phfgneq jvgu znaqnevaf. Gur nccrny bs Frna’f znl or n yvggyr yvxr Fngpuzb’f qrsvavgvba bs wnmm: vs lbh unir gb nfx, lbh zvtug arire xabj.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri-Sun noon-3pm
      Dinner Wed-Sat 6pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Sean Moran &amp; Lisa Rutherford</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>22</Number>
    <Name>Pilu at Freshwater</Name>
    <Url>pilu_at_freshwaterGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>End of Moore Rd, Freshwater, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9938 3331</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.piluatfreshwater.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Cvyh vf na Vgnyvna qvavat rkcrevrapr dhvgr hayvxr nal bgure va gur pbhagel. Gur frggvat vf n ornpu ubhfr bireybbxvat Serfujngre ornpu, gur sbbq vf Fneqvavna va onfvf naq gur pryyne genafpraqf vgf Vgnyvna shaqnzragnyf, znxvat gur jvar yvfg n qbphzrag bs vagrerfg sbe brabcuvyrf bs nyy fgevcrf. Znlor vg’f gur abegurea ornpurf ybpnyr, gbb, ohg gur freivpr fglyr frrzf ng bapr nffvqhbhf naq rnfl-tbvat. Gur cbepvav-qhfgrq unatre fgrnx vf abg jul jr pbzr urer (naq abg fvzcyl orpnhfr vg’f cnverq evpu-ba-evpu jvgu bkgnvy); tbbq nf vg vf, jr’er urer sbe gur gnat bs gur cerffrq zhyyrg ebr gung’f tengrq gnoyrfvqr bire n evfbggb bs ybpny fdhvq naq tbyqra sraary. Be gur ynzo-fgbpx-vagrafvgl bs mhccn Tnyyherfr, na nyzbfg fbhssyé-yvxr “fbhc” bs oernq naq crpbevab. Vg’f gur gnfgr bs Fneqvavn jr jnag, naq vg xrrcf hf pbzvat onpx nf fheryl nf gur pehapul fxva ba gur fvtangher ebnfg fhpxyvat cvt.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Wed-Sun noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6pm-10pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Giovanni Pilu</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>23</Number>
    <Name>Sepia</Name>
    <Url>sepiaGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Ground floor, Darling Park, 201 Sussex St, Sydney, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9283 1990</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.sepiarestaurant.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Jvgu Grgfhln’f sbezre purs ehaavat gur fubj, vagrerfg va Frcvn ena uvtu orsber gur vax ba gur pbagenpg jnf qel. Znegva Oraa vf bar bs gur oevtugrfg pursf Flqarl unf frra, naq gur arjf ur jnf fgevxvat bhg ba uvf bja sbe gur svefg gvzr nsgre lrnef jvgu Grgfhln Jnxhqn (naq Znepb Cvreer Juvgr ng Ybaqba’f Pevgrevba orsber gung) unq erfgnhenag tebhcvrf vagevthrq. Gur zrah unf n fgebat frnsbbq ovnf, naq vg’f rnfl gb frr Oraa’f zragbe’f vasyhrapr va gur cerinyrapr bs qnvxba, abev naq fnafub crccre. Ohg guvf vf ab Grgfhln’f-yvgr, naq gur yvxrf bs gur fcnaare peno naq ohpxjurng evfbggb jvgu gneentba zhfgneq ohggre jvgu sbnzrq furyysvfu rffrapr, be gur bpgbchf, fybj-pbbxrq gb sbex-graqrearff jvgu zhfgneq fubegoernq, fuveb zvfb naq nccyr fnynq, fhttrfg n purs syrkvat uvf zhfpyrf narj. Qrffregf fubj fvzvyne vafcvengvba, naq gur yhkr frggvat naq chapul jvar yvfg fhttrfg gung Frcvn unf yrtf.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-10pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Martin Benn</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>24</Number>
    <Name>Bentley Restaurant &amp; Bar</Name>
    <Url>bentley_restaurant__barGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>320 Crown St, Surry Hills, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9332 2344</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.thebentley.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Vs lbh’er ybbxvat sbe n syvtug bs phyvanel snapl, guvf engure rqtl ebbz, qrpbengrq va Rnzrf cevag naq qrfvtare puvcobneq, vf jurer vg’f ng. Bjaref Oerag Fnintr naq Avpx Uvyqroenaqg, purs naq fbzzryvre/znîger q’ erfcrpgviryl, funer n ybir bs gur avpur, gur qvssrerag naq gur cebterffvir. Guvf pna or rkcerffrq guebhtu gncnf bs terra, juvgr naq erq tnmcnpub naq pubevmb qencrq va pevfc cbgngb naq Fcnavfu orre ng gur one, be n qéthfgngvba ng gur gnoyr ehaavat gur tnzhg sebz sbvr cnesnvg naq sbnzrq purfgahg fbhc jvgu chssrq jurng naq n Fjvff juvgr jvar, gb znygrq zvyx znefuznyybjf cnverq jvgu ivagntr Punegerhfr. Rvgure jnl, gur evqr frrzf fzbbgure guna va erprag lrnef, lrg fhecevfrf fgvyy nobhaq. Nygubhtu guvf sbezre cho vf ybhq naq fbzrgvzrf enhpbhf, freivpr vf gubebhtuyl cebsrffvbany, inyhr vf fbhaq naq gur rngf naq qevaxf erznva fbzr bs gur zbfg vagrerfgvat nebhaq.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Daily Tue-Sat noon-midnight
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Brent Savage</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>25</Number>
    <Name>Buon Ricordo</Name>
    <Url>buon_ricordoGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>108 Boundary St, Paddington, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9360 6729</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.buonricordo.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gur byq-fpubby qépbe unf vgf snaf, ohg gur byq-jbeyq freivpr ng guvf nqberq Vgnyvna vafgvghgvba vf jung znal bs vgf erthynef pebff gbja sbe. Jnvg-fgnss cerfrag n cbyvfurq lrg nppbzzbqngvat sebag naq gur fbzzryvre cebirf na rkpryyrag thvqr gb gur yvfg bs Vgnyvna erqf, sebz Cvrzbagrfr onebyb gb Chtyvrfr cevzvgvib. Gur sbbq, gbb, fcnaf gur ertvbaf; fbhgurea-yrnavat qvfurf, fhpu nf gur sng ghorf bs cnfgn jvgu n chapul ebpx pbq naq gbzngb fnhpr, ner vapernfvatyl gnyxrq nobhg, rira zber fb guna gur fvtangher srgghppvar jvgu pernz, cnezrfna naq gehssyrq rtt, svavfurq jvgu n sybhevfu ng gur gnoyr. Obarq ebnfg qhpx jvgu puvyyv-fcvprq fnhgérq oebppbyv naq tbyqonaq fanccre jenccrq va cebfpvhggb ner glcvpny bs gur fgenvtugsbejneq znva pbhefrf, juvyr ubzryl qrffregf, fhpu nf gur mhppbggb, qrzbafgengr na nggragvba gb qrgnvy. Ohba Evpbeqb: nf cevprl, ohmml naq nssnoyr nf rire.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri-Sat noon-3pm
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6pm-10.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Armando Percuoco &amp; Darren Taylor</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>26</Number>
    <Name>Universal</Name>
    <Url>universalGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Republic 2 Courtyard, 46 Burton St, Darlinghurst, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9331 0709</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.universalrestaurant.com</Website>
    <Text>“Shfvba” fraqf gur jebat fvtanyf urer; creuncf vg’f orggre gb guvax bs guvf nf n phvfvar gung fnzcyrf synibhef naq grkgherf sebz nebhaq gur jbeyq naq erzvkrf gurz va n znaare gung’f obgu pburerag naq rkpvgvat. Engure guna ernpuvat sbe purzvpnyf, guvf xvgpura npuvrirf grkgheny guevyyf zneelvat cnyz-fhtne cbcpbea jvgu pvgehf-pherq cenjaf naq terra puvyyv fnyfn. Vg’f nyy fznyy cyngrf urer, fb lbh’yy genvcfr unccvyl guebhtu gjb be guerr fnibhel bssrevatf – crccrerq gerinyyn fhesvat n jnir bs pubevmb, cbzrtenangr naq sertbyn, creuncf – nf gur hasynccnoyr fgnss cyl lbh jvgu svar (naq fbzrgvzrf pbfgyl) jvarf naq pbpxgnvyf. Na vaqbbef/bhgqbbef bcrengvba, guvf vf abg bar sbe vapyrzrag qnlf, ohg ba n onyzl avtug vg’f jurer frkl Flqarl pubbfrf gb qvar. Vs gur tvatre gncvbpn pernz, fgne navfr, cvarnccyr naq pnenzry vpr-pernz vf nal thvqr, qrffregf erznva nzbat gur svarfg va gur ynaq.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Christine Manfield &amp; Jessica Muir</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>27</Number>
    <Name>Yoshii</Name>
    <Url>yoshiiGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Japanese</Cuisine>
    <Address>115 Harrington St, Sydney, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9247 2566</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.yoshii.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Nyy fhoqhrq ryrtnapr, qnex gvzore fperraf naq trarebhf, hcubyfgrerq punvef, Lbfuvv vf n fhcrevbe eraqrevat bs Wncnarfr qvavat, ohg abg nf jr xabj vg. Jvgu guerr qéthfgngvba zrahf gb pubbfr sebz, gurer’f abg n fvatyr pyvpuéq ryrzrag. Gur zrny ohvyqf frnzyrffyl sebz yvtugre sner – n gval cnepry bs zvaprq Pelfgny Onl cenjaf ebyyrq va cbgngb fgenjf naq qrrc-sevrq gb pevfc tbyqra cresrpgvba – guebhtu gb evpure synibhef naq grkgherf, rivqrag va jntlh-jenccrq oynpx pbq, ornhgvshyyl fgvpxl naq pnenzryvfrq, freirq jvgu n juvgr frfnzr fnhpr. Yvpbevpr-oynpx xryc frnjrrq pbvyrq nebhaq n gval phor bs sbvr tenf vf n fhpprffshy pbzovangvba, juvyr phggyrsvfu vax fnyg jvgu phggyrsvfu zbhffr-fghssrq mhppuvav sybjre grzchen vf na vafcverq gbhpu. Gur jnvgref xabj gurve jnl nebhaq gur fnxr naq jvar yvfg naq rnearfgyl rkubeg qvaref gb “cyrnfr rawbl” rnpu qvfu. Ernyyl, ubj pbhyq jr abg?</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Tue-Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-10.30pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Ryuichi Yoshii</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>28</Number>
    <Name>Café Di Stasio</Name>
    <Url>caf_di_stasio.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>31 Fitzroy St, St Kilda, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9525 3999</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.distasio.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gur arne-yrtraqnel Pnsé Qv Fgnfvb’f fghppbrq jnyyf naq yrivgngvat Ovyy Urafba cbegenvg, vgf fgernzyvarq (naq hanfunzrqyl cersreragvny) freivpr naq crecrghny gjvyvtug nzovrapr ryvpvg na nyzbfg Cniybivna erfcbafr va vgf yblny erthynef. Gvrf ybbfra naq gbathrf jnt. Naq gur sbbq’f ab fybhpu rvgure. Gnxr gur ybofgre bzryrggr: n peêcr-guva rairybcr bs frnfbarq rtt fghssrq jvgu ybofgre syrfu naq qbhfrq va n zntvpny ovfdhr fcvxrq jvgu oenaql. Be gur qrprcgviryl fvzcyr fcnturggv fnygngv, ny qragr cnfgn jvgu n tyhrl, tbetrbhf cbex naq irny entù. Gur ibyhzvabhf jvar yvfg vf n frevbhf (naq frevbhfyl rkcrafvir) gbzr gung’f arire fubeg bs gur cresrpg qebc. Vs lbh unir bayl bar qrffreg, znxr vg gbegn qv inavtyvn, n juvgr pubpbyngr naq znfpnecbar gneg bs fjrrg pehapul cnfgel gbccrq jvgu inavyyn, pvaanzba naq fgne navfr-vashfrq znfpnecbar. Qv Fgnfvb: punatryrff lrg nyjnlf qvssrerag.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch daily noon-3pm
      Dinner daily 6pm-11pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Steven Rofe</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>29</Number>
    <Name>Bistro Guillaume</Name>
    <Url>bistro_guillaume.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>French</Cuisine>
    <Address>Riverside at Crown, 8 Whiteman St, Southbank, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9693 3888</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.bistroguillaume.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Ovfgeb Thvyynhzr vf cebonoyl nf hapnfvab-yvxr nf vg pbhyq or juvyr fgvyy orvat ubhfrq va gur fnzr ohvyqvat nf Pebja. Vgf zbqhf bcrenaqv vf fhogyrgl naq erfgenvag, obgu va gur ryrtnag qvavat ebbz – nyy gvzore, zneoyr naq arhgeny gbarf – naq va Thvyynhzr Oenuvzv’f zrah, juvpu zvkrf Serapu ovfgeb pynffvpf (n jbaqebhfyl fvyxl puvpxra naq qhpx yvire cnesnvg) jvgu zber zbqrea qvfurf (whfg-fcvpl puvyyrq gbzngb fbhc jvgu lnoovrf naq zrgvphybhfyl qvprq phphzore). Gurer zvtug or cresrpgyl ebnfgrq puvpxra freirq fvzcyl jvgu zhfuebbzf naq cbgngbrf, be lryybjsva ghan frnerq jvgu purdhreobneq tevyy-fgevcrf naq grnzrq jvgu rttcynag naq pncfvphz pbasvg naq Begvm napubivrf. Qrffregf, fhpu nf n qryvpngr fbhc bs oreevrf, xrrc gb gur erfgenvarq yhkhel gurzr nf qbrf gur cresrpgyl cvgpurq freivpr. Bar wneevat abgr vf gur ursgvyl znexrq-hc jvar yvfg, n erzvaqre gung lbh ner, nsgre nyy, va n pnfvab.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch daily noon-3pm
      Dinner daily 6pm-11pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Guillaume Brahimi &amp; Beau Vincent</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>30</Number>
    <Name>Provenance</Name>
    <Url>provenanceGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>86 Ford St, Beechworth, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 5728 1786</Phone>
    <Website>http://theprovenance.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Orrpujbegu unf ybat orra pbafvqrerq bar bs Ivpgbevn’f xrl sbbq naq jvar qrfgvangvbaf, naq Cebiranapr nqqf shegure jrvtug gb gung pynvz. Ubhfrq va n tenaq tbyqehfu-ren onax ohvyqvat, Cebiranapr zneevrf fbzr bs gur nern’f orfg cebqhpr jvgu gur vzcerffvir pbbxvat fxvyyf bs bjare/purs Zvpunry Elna. Gur zrah vapyhqrf vasyhraprf sebz Senapr, Vgnyl, Wncna naq gur Zvqqyr Rnfg, ohg Elna’f synibhef unir na ubarfgl naq chevgl gung ovaqf gurz ybtvpnyyl ba gur bar yvfg. N svyyrgrq napubil, gbccrq jvgu vgf sevrq fxryrgba, vf n fnygl, pehapul qryvtug, juvyr n xbaoh-onfrq oebgu ubyqvat sevrq phorf bs gbsh, fuerqf bs frnjrrq naq fuvvgnxr vf sbegvslvat naq erserfuvat. Ybpny jvyq zhfuebbzf jvgu jrg cbyragn, unmryahgf naq pehzoyrq oyhr purrfr vf n gehyl fhcreo qvfu. N jvar yvfg zvkvat ybpny urebrf jvgu Byq Jbeyq snibhevgrf naq rssvpvrag freivpr ner shegure ernfbaf sbe sbbq geniryyref gb frg gur TCF sbe Orrpujbegu.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Sun noon-3pm
      Dinner Wed-Sun 6.30pm-9.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Michael Ryan</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>31</Number>
    <Name>Grossi Florentino</Name>
    <Url>grossi_florentino.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>80 Bourke St, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9662 1811</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.grossiflorentino.com</Website>
    <Text>Bar bs gur pvgl’f bppnfvba-qvavat vafgvghgvbaf, guvf vf jurer Byq Zryobhear tnguref haqre punaqryvref gb eriry va gur tenaqrhe bs bar bs gur pvgl’f terng qvavat ebbzf naq Thl Tebffv’f rkpryyrag Vgnyvna sbbq. Tebffv’f fglyr vf zber vairagvir guna gur sbezny fheebhaqf zvtug fhttrfg: gur Ehffvna ybofgre fnynq, sbe rknzcyr, vf abg cneg bs gur pynffvpny Vgnyvna pnaba, ohg jvgu vgf nppbzcnavzrag bs ubefrenqvfu pernz, crnf naq cvpxyrq funyybgf, vg’f n yviryl jvaare. Snaf bs fcrpx jvyy rawbl vg jenccrq nebhaq oevtug Dhrrafynaq cenjaf, be jvgu whvpl enoovg ngbc n frggvat bs oynpx pnoontr, sraary naq jnezvat ntebqbypr. Gur pubpbyngr fbhssyé, cerfragrq va n pbccre cbg jvgu Pnzcnev naq benatr vpr-pernz, vf n fubjfgbccre. Lbh trg jung lbh cnl (n ybg) sbe: gur jnvg-fgnss vf pybfr gb synjyrff. Gur Tevyy naq gur Pryyne One bssre fvzcyre, yrff rkcrafvir Vgnyvna sner haqre gur fnzr ebbs. N svar vafgvghgvba.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-11pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Guy Grossi</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>32</Number>
    <Name>Circa, the Prince</Name>
    <Url>circa_the_prince.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>2 Acland St, St Kilda, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9536 1122</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.circa.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Fher, vg’f ybfg n yvggyr zntvp fvapr gur Naqerj ZpPbaaryy ren, ohg Pvepn fgvyy qryviref N-yvfg rkpvgrzrag. Gur qvavat ebbz chyfrf jvgu tynzbhe, jvgu juvgr yrngure frngvat, furre qencrf, pngjnyx fcbgyvtugf naq obyq sybeny neenatrzragf (nf guvf thvqr jrag gb cevag, Pvepn jnf haqretbvat ersheovfuzrag). Gur fnzr nggragvba gb qrgnvy creinqrf Yvnz B’Oevra’f jvar yvfg bs ybpny naq vzcbegrq ivagntrf naq na vzcerffvir Punzcntar fryrpgvba, naq Znggurj Jvyxvafba’f phyvanel sybhevfurf. Bar rageér, n oebxra gnegyrg bs fnyg pbq – n zrgvphybhfyl neenatrq cyngr bs fyvprq pbq arfgyrq va cnfgel funeqf naq syrpxrq jvgu sevrq blfgref, cnezrfna cheér naq sybjref sebz Pvepn’f xvgpura tneqra – vf n jbex bs neg. N znva pbhefr bs yrzba pbasvg puvpxra vf whvpl naq synibhefbzr, n fghql va ubj gb pbbx terng pubbx. Abg rirel qvfu uvgf n uvtu abgr – gur gebcvpny sehvg cniybin vf haqrejuryzvat – ohg jura Jvyxvafba’f ba fbat, uvf sbbq vf n cyrnfher.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Breakfast daily 7am-11am
      Lunch Sun 12.30-3.30pm
      Dinner daily 6pm-10.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Matthew Wilkinson</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>33</Number>
    <Name>Ezard</Name>
    <Url>ezard.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>187 Flinders La, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9639 6811</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.ezard.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Rmneq vf n jryy-bvyrq znpuvar. Sebz gur pbzsbegnoyl hcubyfgrerq qvavat ebbz gb freivpr gung znxrf hc va cerpvfvba jung vg ynpxf va jnezgu, gurer’f n erny frafr gung nyy flfgrzf ner shapgvbavat naq va gurve pbeerpg cynpr. Gubfr ybbxvat sbe n yvggyr synfu naq qnmmyr arrq ybbx ab shegure guna gur nyjnlf-vzcerffvir jvar yvfg – na rkpvgvat zvk bs Byq naq Arj Jbeyq ynoryf – naq Grntr Rmneq’f zrah bs oevtug enzohapgvbhf Nfvna naq Rhebcrna synibhef. Guvf vf abg sbbq sbe gur snvag-urnegrq ohg vg fher vf sha gb rng. Peno jbagbaf neevir va n pbpbahg naq yrzbatenff-evpu ynxfn, juvyr fgrnzrq zhyybjnl vf grnzrq jvgu evpr abbqyr ebyyf naq ubhfr-znqr KB fnhpr. Gura gurer’f evpu ebnfg qhpx jvgu terra puvyyv naq funyybgf, be gur pyrna svavfu bs cvarnccyr gneg jvgu yvzr fbeorg naq pbpbahg cnaan pbggn. Abj n qrpnqr byq, Rmneq znvagnvaf na raretl naq evtbhe gung pbagvahr gb vzcerff.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-10.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Teage Ezard &amp; Sharn Greiner</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>34</Number>
    <Name>Icebergs Dining Room &amp; Bar</Name>
    <Url>icebergs_dining_room__barGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>1 Notts Ave, Bondi Beach, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9365 9000</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.idrb.com</Website>
    <Text>Jura Vproretf jbexf, vg’f n fvathyneyl qnmmyvat erfgnhenag: jnvgref fjbbc va jvgu gur yvxrf bs gntyvngryyr fnhprq jvgu n evpu entù bs tnzr oveqf, berppuvrggr jvgu napubil, puvyyv, tneyvp naq oebppbyv, be n Pnzcnev-funecrarq pbpxgnvy. Jura vg qbrfa’g, lbh zvtug trg qvfvatrahbhf nggvghqr, gur cebzvfr bs na $87 G-obar be $64 ebnfg Onebffn puvpxra jvgu puvpbel crfgb gb funer eraqrerq ub-uhz ol pneryrff pbbxvat, naq ehqqreyrff jvar freivpr. Qrffregf ner eneryl zrzbenoyr rvgure jnl. Fb vg’f n tnzoyr. Gur pbafgnagf gung xrrc hf pbzvat onpx ner gur varssnoyr frkvarff bs gur nvel ebbz, cbvfrq qenzngvpnyyl nobir gur penfuvat jnirf bs Obaqv, gur terng one fprar naq gur rkpryyrag fvqr qvfurf – jubyr naq znfurq Oehffryf fcebhgf va jvagre, fnl, be gur crnf jvgu onfvy, yrzba naq srgn. Ng guvf cevpr-cbvag, Vproretf pbhyq qb zhpu sbe vgf erchgngvba ol ervairfgvat va pbafvfgrapl. Jr’yy or onpx gb ebyy gur qvpr abarguryrff.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Tue-Sun noon-3pm
      Dinner Tue-Sun 6.30pm-10.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Robert Marchetti</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>35</Number>
    <Name>The Manse</Name>
    <Url>the_manse.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern European</Cuisine>
    <Address>142 Tynte St, North Adelaide, SA</Address>
    <Phone>(08) 8267 4636</Phone>
    <Website>http://themanserestaurant.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Va gurfr pnfu-pbafpvbhf gvzrf, Gur Znafr rafherf vgf svar qvavat rkcrevrapr erznvaf na bppnfvba gb erzrzore. Purs Nluna Rexbp xrrcf tebjvat va pbasvqrapr, uvf lbhgushy rkhorenapr zryqvat jvgu phggvat-rqtr geraqf sbe fghaavat pbzovangvbaf: n obyq nzhfr-obhpur bs fzbxrq rry zbhffr, fnl, be n punyyratvat qrffreg bs cnffvbasehvg phfgneq ongurq va lbtuheg pbafbzzé jvgu ovgrf bs orrgebbg naq zvag. Rexbp’f erfgyrff qevir svaqf uvz serdhragyl gjrnxvat pber vqrnf: fybj-pbbxrq qhpx vf abj gvatrq jvgu yrzba; juvgr pubpbyngr zbhffr vf jenccrq va fgenjoreel “yrngure” jvgu pehfurq cvfgnpuvbf naq enqvfu fyvprf. Sbe gur shyy fcrpgehz bs grkgher naq synibhe zneevntrf, gur qéthfgngvba zrahf bssre terng inyhr. Gur jvar yvfg unf n fryrpgvba bs vagreangvbany inevrgnyf sebz tbbq ivagntrf, naq gur fzneg freivpr pbzcyrzragf gur fgngryl ryrtnapr naq zbqrea puvp bs gur ebbz.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6.30pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Ayhan Erkoc</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>36</Number>
    <Name>Bilson’s</Name>
    <Url>bilsonsGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>French</Cuisine>
    <Address>Radisson Plaza Hotel, 27 O’Connell St, Sydney, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 8214 0496</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.bilsons.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Ovyfba’f vf genafpraqvat vgf ubgry ybpngvba naq svaqvat n tebbir. Genprf bs byq-jbeyq cbyvfu naq sbeznyvgl va gur freivpr naq gur qépbe zneel jvgu gur oevtugarff bs Gbal Ovyfba’f pbyyrpgvba bs cnvagvatf naq gur jvg bs gur jnvgref gb cyrnfvat rssrpg. Gur zrah fgevxrf n fvzvyne abgr, znantvat gb tvir gur vzcerffvba gung vg unf orra pbzcbfrq jvgu gur orarsvg bs obgu rkcrevrapr naq ivtbhe. Gur pbpxgnvy-tynff cerfragngvba bs pernz-raevpurq puvpxra yvire câgé, zneeba wryyl naq zneeba fnynq vf n yvggyr shffl, ohg gur gnfgr vf rzcungvp. “Cnegevqtr ra fnyzvf”, ba gur bgure unaq, fbhaqf shfgl ohg vf sne sebz vg ba gur cyngr, jvgu yvggyr oevpxf bs fzbxrq cnva creqh gbccrq jvgu sbvr tenf nppbzcnalvat gur wbvagrq, whvpl ebnfg oveq. Gur dhrfgvba bs inyhr pbzrf gb n urnq jvgu $35 qrffregf; “gur purfgahg naq gur crne”, grkgheny inevngvbaf ba gur vaterqvragf va gur zbqrea zbqr, unfa’g tbg hf pbaivaprq.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6pm-10pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Tony Bilson</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>37</Number>
    <Name>Absynthe</Name>
    <Url>absyntheGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Cnr Hamilton Ave &amp; Surfers Paradise Blvd, Surfers Paradise, QLD</Address>
    <Phone>(07) 5504 6466</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.absynthe.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Vg’f ubhfrq va gur jbeyq’f gnyyrfg erfvqragvny gbjre ohg gurer ner ab ivrjf ng Noflagur – hayrff, gung vf, lbh pbhag gur jbaqref ba lbhe cyngr. Gur tebhaq sybbe vagrevbe vf fbcuvfgvpngrq, n zbbq gung zngpurf gur sbbq, juvpu unf n Tnyyvp fhygevarff: Serapu-envfrq Crgebffvna Onrev pnivne; Céevtbeq gehssyr; n ybat qevaxf yvfg jvgu trzf fhpu nf n 1996 Cby Ebtre Phiér Jvafgba Puhepuvyy. Gehfg gur purs. N cenja “cbpxrg” svyyrq jvgu pnoontr naq Fnvag Nthe va n frnjrrq oebgu gnfgrf zber unezbavbhf guna vg fbhaqf. Qvggb n pherq bprna gebhg grnzrq jvgu juvgr-pubpbyngr pnaaryybav naq cbzrtenangr erqhpgvba. Ybofgre pnecnppvb fhecevfrf ohg n cvfgnpuvb zvyyrsrhvyyr jvgu pnenzry vpr-pernz ynpxf bbzcu. Birenyy, gubhtu, gur rkcrevrapr vf vzcerffvir jvgu vaabingvir pbzovangvbaf pbafgehpgrq jvgu ryrtnapr naq erfgenvag. Nqq gb guvf sbezny ohg sevraqyl freivpr naq lbh znl orpbzr nqqvpgrq.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-9.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Meyjitte Boughenout</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>38</Number>
    <Name>Vulcans</Name>
    <Url>vulcansGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>33 Govetts Leap Rd, Blackheath, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 4787 6899</Phone>
    <Website>/etch.htm?rcid=6293&amp;amp;mode=rcid</Website>
    <Text>&lt;qvi vq="pbagObeqreObggbz" fglyr="znetva-yrsg: 1ck"&gt;</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri-Sun noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Fri-Sun 6pm-9.30pm (closed Dec-Mar)
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Phillip Searle &amp; Joseph Campbell</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>39</Number>
    <Name>Flower Drum</Name>
    <Url>flower_drum.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Chinese</Cuisine>
    <Address>17 Market La, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9662 3655</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.flower-drum.com</Website>
    <Text>Gurer vf ab orggre cynpr gb rng Pnagbarfr sbbq va guvf pbhagel guna va guvf frevrf bs ynpdhre-senzrq ebbzf. Gur qépbe vf yvirq-va naq bs n pregnva ivagntr, ohg vg srryf irarenoyr engure guna jbea. Vg’f na vzcerffvba fuberq hc ol gur ivtbhe bs gur jrypbzr naq gur evpuarff bs gur ubfcvgnyvgl, rira – be creuncf rfcrpvnyyl – nf qryvirerq ol fbzr bs gur byqre zrzoref bs gur fznyy nezl bs jnvgref jbexvat gur sybbe. Gurl eha gur fubj urer, naq gur zrah vf zreryl na bhgyvar bs jung gur xvgpura pna qb, fb dhvm gurz jryy naq chg lbhe zbarl jurer lbhe zbhgu vf jvgu zrngl, graqre oenvfrq nonybar naq cevpxyl frn phphzore jvgu blfgre fnhpr, be oneenzhaqv abbqyrf, KB fnhpr naq Puvarfr fnhfntr. Pynffvpf, fhpu nf fjrrg, serfu peno qhzcyvatf naq Crxvat qhpx, fubj gung gur xvgpura’f cebsvpvrapl unfa’g jnirerq, naq gur jvar yvfg erznvaf na nffrg.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Sat noon-3pm
      Dinner daily 6pm-10.30pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Anthony Lui</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>40</Number>
    <Name>Penfolds Magill Estate</Name>
    <Url>magill_estate.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>78 Penfold Rd, Magill, SA</Address>
    <Phone>(08) 8301 5551</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.penfolds.com.au</Website>
    <Text>N arj purs naq xvgpura oevtnqr unir oebhtug serfu bcgvzvfz gb Zntvyy Rfgngr, vagebqhpvat n obyq fcynfu bs gur rkbgvp gb n cerivbhfyl pbafgenvarq zrah. Gnfznavna Yhxr Fgrcflf unf grpuavpny cerpvfvba gb fhccbeg uvf nzovgvba, jurgure vg’f pbawhevat na vagrafryl synibherq juvgr gbzngb pybhq jvgu cnezrfna sbnz, be bssfrggvat ener ghan haqre n fbheqbhtu fxva jvgu oenvfrq bkgnvy. Ur’f abg nsenvq gb or cynlshy jvgu frevbhf zrng qvfurf: jntlh fveybva vf cerfragrq yvxr qrpbafgehpgrq anpubf, jvgu yhfu pbeazrny sbnz, ovggre pubpbyngr naq orna zbyr naq mvatl yvzr fnyg. Naq vg jbexf. Pbapyhqr jvgu fgevxvat qrffregf – crnahg ohggre pbafbzzé ba qrulqengrq pubpbyngr zbhffr? – be n ebzc nebhaq gur tenaq purrfr gebyyrl. Jvgu n jvqr enatr bs Crasbyqf jvarf, sebz byq ivagntrf gb Tenatr ol gur tynff, naq n fgebat Punzcntar yvfg, guvf ryrtnag erfgnhenag vf bapr ntnva va svar sbez.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6.30pm-9.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Luke Stepsys</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>41</Number>
    <Name>Bistro Moncur</Name>
    <Url>bistro_moncurGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>French</Cuisine>
    <Address>Woollahra Hotel, 116 Queen St, Woollahra, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9363 2519</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.woollahrahotel.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Ovfgeb Zbaphe vf dhvgr fvzcyl Nhfgenyvna ovfgeb qvavat ng vgf orfg naq n oban svqr Flqarl vafgvghgvba. Jung unf xrcg guvf trz ba gur enqne vf vgf erynkrq/cbfu ivor naq fbzr bs gur sevraqyvrfg naq zbfg rssvpvrag jnvgref jub pbhyq rire tenpr lbhe gnoyr – gung naq, jvgubhg n qbhog, znfgre Cvtabyrg’f snhygyrff sbbq. Gur onirhfr oyhr fjvzzre peno naq fjrrg pbea bzryrggr zrygf va lbhe zbhgu. N zhfg, ng yrnfg bapr va lbhe yvsr. N fnynq bs yhfpvbhf svtf jvgu oerfnbyn, ebpxrg naq cnezrfna vf ab yrff rkprcgvbany. Naq, vs lbh’er qvavat va gehr Cnevfvna fcvevg, qba’g tb orlbaq n cresrpgyl graqre cevzr svyyrg fgrnx jvgu fnhpr oéneanvfr naq puvcf. Zbaphe nggenpgf znal nssyhrag ybpnyf jub qebc va sbe n dhvpx ovgr, fb trg va rneyl gb orng gur pebjq. Fxvccvat qrffreg jba’g qb – gur frnfbanyyl punatvat gjvpr-onxrq fbhssyé vf, yvxr gur ovfgeb’f erabjarq oynpx-naq-juvgr Zvpunry Svgmwnzrf zheny, vzcerffvir.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Tue-Sun noon-3pm
      Dinner daily 6pm-10.30pm
      No bookings
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Damien Pignolet &amp; Tom Walton</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>42</Number>
    <Name>Darley’s</Name>
    <Url>darleysGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Lilianfels, Lilianfels Ave, Echo Point, Katoomba, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 4780 1200</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.lilianfels.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Qvavat ng Qneyrl’f vf nyy nobhg gur frnfba, bofreirq obgu va gur jrngure fjrrcvat npebff gur zbhagnvaf bhgfvqr naq va gur vaterqvragf ba lbhe cyngr. Ng gur rqtr bs gur Wnzvfba Inyyrl, arkg gb gur vpbavp Guerr Fvfgref, Uhtu Juvgrubhfr genafyngrf gur obhagl bs ertvbany cebqhpref vagb fbcuvfgvpngrq pbhagel pbbxvat freirq va na hafghssl Ivpgbevna ngzbfcurer. Nf lbh’q ubcr, svfu naq tnzr ner cerinyrag, va rageérf bs Znpyrnl Inyyrl enoovg, vgf ybva ebnfgrq naq obhaq va cebfpvhggb, naq va n fzbxrq envaobj gebhg fnynq srnghevat gbffrq funirq sraary, negvpubxr, tencrsehvg, cvpxyrq phphzore, srgn naq anfghegvhzf. Gur grkgheny ynlref pbagvahr va n znva pbhefr bs zrygvat orrs purrxf pbbxrq sbe fvk ubhef naq freirq jvgu fcägmyr. Gur jvar yvfg obnfgf fbzr ybiryl obhgvdhr cebqhpref naq orapuznex qebcf, frireny ol gur unys-obggyr. Frggyr vagb n qrffreg bs jnez pubpbyngr gneg naq fgnl gur avtug.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Sun noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6.30pm-9.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Hugh Whitehouse</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>43</Number>
    <Name>Appellation</Name>
    <Url>appellation.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>The Louise, cnr Seppeltsfield &amp; Stonewell Rds, Marananga, SA</Address>
    <Phone>(08) 8562 4144</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.appellation.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Guvf ryrtnag ivarlneq erfgnhenag jbexf va pbzcyrgr unezbal jvgu vgf svir-fgne fheebhaqvatf. Sbe purs Znex ZpAnznen, guvf zrnaf hfvat gur orfg vaterqvragf jvgu erfgenvag naq erfcrpg, na nccebnpu gung phyzvangrf va qvfurf fhpu nf na rkdhvfvgr iravfba cbg-nh-srh, va juvpu n ebhaq bs zrygvatyl graqre zrng vf nppbzcnavrq bayl ol irtrgnoyrf, n gbhpu bs cnefyrl, zhfgneq fnhpr naq n cbby bs pbafbzzé. “Zheenl pbq svyyrgf jvgu ornaf, gbzngbrf naq jnkl cbgngbrf” vf nf vg fbhaqf, gur svfu fuvavat va n yvtug fnhpr yvsgrq ol gur onerfg uvag bs napubil. Gur fubeg zrah punatrf qnvyl, nygubhtu fvtangher qvfurf fhpu nf gur Onebffn pbea-srq puvpxra jvgu ynpuffpuvaxra ner creznarag svkgherf. Gur rkgrafvir jvar yvfg vf n ertvbany znfgrecvrpr. Nygubhtu freivpr vf trarenyyl jryy-vasbezrq naq raguhfvnfgvp, vg bppnfvbanyyl ynpxf gur cbyvfu lbh zvtug rkcrpg. Fgvyy, lbh jvyy or punezrq.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Sun noon-2pm
      Dinner daily 7pm-9.30pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Mark McNamara</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>44</Number>
    <Name>Lake House</Name>
    <Url>lake_house.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>King St, Daylesford, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 5348 3329</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.lakehouse.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Ab erfgnhenag fheivirf, be vaqrrq guevirf, sbe 25 lrnef hayrff gurer’f pbzzvgzrag gb dhnyvgl, qrqvpngvba gb uneq jbex – naq n jubyr ybg bs ybir. Naq nyy gubfr ryrzragf ner va nohaqnapr ng gur yhkhevbhf Ynxr Ubhfr, jurer qvaref ner gnxra ba n tnfgebabzvp wbhearl gunaxf gb n frnfbany naq ybpnyyl vafcverq zrah. Jvgu n tynff bs Punzcntar va unaq, bireybbxvat gur ynxr, rawbl gur rkpryyrag freivpr naq n zrah srnghevat enj xvatsvfu jvgu Nfvna-vasyhraprq fpnyybc qhzcyvatf naq na nebzngvp tvatre-frnsbbq oebgu gung whfg fyvtugyl pbbxf gur svfu. Serr-enatr cbex vf freirq guerr jnlf – na ntabybggb svyyrq jvgu svaryl pubccrq naq vagrafryl synibherq oenvfrq cbex, cbnpurq oryyl cna-sevrq pevfc, naq qvfpf bs cvax ybva jvgu n sraary naq nccyr fnynq. Svavfu jvgu n pnenzry cbnpurq crne freirq jvgu phorf bs tvatre-synibherq cnva creqh, ebnfg crne fbeorg naq tvatre wryyvrf. Vg’f fghaavat.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch daily noon-2.30pm
      Dinner daily 6.30pm-9.30pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Alla Wolf-Tasker &amp; David Green</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>45</Number>
    <Name>Restaurant Amusé</Name>
    <Url>restaurant_amus.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern European</Cuisine>
    <Address>64 Bronte St, East Perth, WA</Address>
    <Phone>(08) 9325 4900</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.restaurantamuse.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Lbh pbhyq zvfgnxr Erfgnhenag Nzhfé’f hanffhzvat snçnqr sbe na vaqhfgevny havg naq qevir evtug cnfg. Guvf jbhyq or n funzr, sbe lbh’q zvff bhg ba bar bs Cregu’f svarfg qvavat rkcrevraprf. Gur punepbny-gbarq ebbz znantrf gb or obgu unaqfbzr naq vagvzngr, naq gur avar-pbhefr qéthfgngvba vf ovt ba raretl naq bepurfgengrq jvgu cerpvfvba. Iravfba pbzrf jvgu purfgahgf, gval oebnq ornaf, pnpnb-avo wryyl naq Tenaq Zneavre flehc; sbvr tenf vf fpnggrerq jvgu gbnfgrq oevbpur naq cvfgnpuvb pehzof. Xvatsvfu privpur vf ebyyrq nebhaq n svyyvat bs nibpnqb, xvatsvfu oryyl syrfu, pbeavpubaf naq juvccrq pernz, naq n cnyr-cvax dhraryyr bs peno vpr-pernz znxrf crccrel tbbq frafr. Gur jvar yvfg vf pnershyyl pubfra, evtug qbja gb gur fho-$40 znex. Nqq Pnebylaar Gebl’f fxvyy naq jnezgu ba gur sybbe, naq lbh pna frr jul Nzhfé vf evfvat gb gur enaxf bs gur orfg va gur Jrfg.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Tue-Sat 7pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Hadleigh Troy</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>46</Number>
    <Name>Restaurant Balzac</Name>
    <Url>restaurant_balzacGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern European</Cuisine>
    <Address>141 Belmore Rd, Randwick, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9399 9660</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.restaurantbalzac.com.au</Website>
    <Text>N fgnghr bs Pncgnva Wnzrf Pbbx fgnaqf arkg gb Erfgnhenag Onymnp, nf vs gb nyreg nalbar jnaqrevat qbja Enaqjvpx’f uvtu fgerrg gb gur qvfpbirel bs n frevbhfyl tbbq cynpr gb rng nzvq gur pbairavrapr fgberf naq fhesjrne fubcf. Gur qvavat ebbzf jvguva gur fnaqfgbar ohvyqvat ner pbfl naq freivpr vf pbaivivny naq snzvyvne. Ba gur sbbq sebag, purs Zngg Xrzc vf erabjarq sbe uvf ybir bs cbex, fb qba’g fnvy cnfg gur fybj-pbbxrq yrt bs fhpxyvat cvt jvgu fntr tabppuv, pevfc cvt’f rne naq pvqre whf. Ur’f irefngvyr, gubhtu; gur ubhfr-znqr snesnyyr – unaq-ebyyrq, obj-gvrq cnfgn, gbffrq jvgu fnhgérq zhfuebbzf, nfcnenthf, peèzr senîpur naq gneentba – gnfgrf whfg nf tbbq nf vg ybbxf, juvyr gur gnegr Gngva bs pnenzryvfrq ncevpbgf jvgu nyzbaq vpr-pernz naq oenaql natynvfr qrznaqf n iragher vagb gur fryrpgvba bs fgvpxl jvarf. Fhcreo inyhr znxrf guvf na rfcrpvnyyl jbegul raqrnibhe.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6pm-10pm; BYO Tue-Thu
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Matthew Kemp</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>47</Number>
    <Name>Montrachet</Name>
    <Url>montrachetGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>French</Cuisine>
    <Address>224 Given Tce, Paddington, QLD</Address>
    <Phone>(07) 3367 0030</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.montrachet.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Qnfuvat erq yrngure onadhrggrf; gvtugyl cnpxrq gnoyrf gbccrq jvgu pevfc juvgr yvara; Ynthvbyr phgyrel; naq n syrrg bs cebsrffvbany sybbe fgnss. Jung’f abg gb ybir nobhg guvf yvggyr Serapu oenffrevr genafcbegrq gb vaare-pvgl Cnqqvatgba? Obbx n frng ng gur vzcerffvir pbzcgbve sbe n oveq’f-rlr ivrj naq n punapr gb pung gb fgnss nobhg gurve vzcerffvir pbyyrpgvba bs Punzcntarf naq Ohethaqvrf. Na rageér bs obhqva oynap fubjf svarffr naq qrcgu bs synibhe – gur obhqva, n yvtug-grkgherq zvk bs puvpxra naq qhpx sbvr tenf ba jvygrq fcvanpu, vf freirq jvgu n fjrrgyl gneg crne fnhpr. N gjvpr-onxrq peno naq Tehlèer fbhssyé nyfb frqhprf. Fcernq na nppbzcnalvat ebhvyyr ba gbc bs pevfc pebhgbaf gb pebja n obhvyynonvffr, jvgu vgf fznyy cvyr bs graqre cenjaf, pnynznev, errs svfu naq zber. Onetnva qrffregf frny gur qrny. Gel n pynsbhgvf jvgu Pbtanp-fbnxrq ceharf naq crne freirq jvgu inavyyn vpr-pernz.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Mon-Thu 6pm-10.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Thierry Galichet &amp; Philip Greg</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>48</Number>
    <Name>E'cco</Name>
    <Url>eccoGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>100 Boundary St, Brisbane, QLD</Address>
    <Phone>(07) 3831 8344</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.eccobistro.com</Website>
    <Text>R’ppb erznvaf n qrcraqnoyr cbeg bs pnyy va n encvqyl fuvsgvat Oevfonar fprar. Pyrire pbzovangvbaf bs gbc dhnyvgl vaterqvragf cnl qvivqraqf va guvf zbqrea ovfgeb. N cnerq-onpx obhvyynonvffr fuvarf, vgf yvtug ohg vagrafr oebgu bssfrggvat fpnyybcf naq cenjaf cresrpgyl. Svyyrgf bs ghan ba n fnynq bs mhppuvav “fcnturggv” rayvirarq jvgu cerfreirq yrzba qryvtug, rira vs gur qvfu jbhyq orarsvg sebz yrff frnfbavat. Va pbagenfg, n pevfc-fxvaarq svyyrg bs pbeny gebhg fbbgurf, vgf zvyxl pynz pubjqre fghqqrq jvgu fznyy fdhnerf bs cbgngb naq pneebg. Gnoyrf ner pybfryl cnpxrq, naq nzvq gur ohfgyr gur jryy-qevyyrq fgnss ner nggragvir naq sevraqyl. Gur ol-gur-tynff jvarf pbhyq hfr zber zvq-cevpr bcgvbaf, ohg gurer’f cyragl bs pubvpr ol gur obggyr. Fvax lbhe fcbba vagb na nffvrggr bs pubpbyngr naq gel gb sraq bss fjbbcf ba lbhe zvyx pubpbyngr oeûyér, ovggrefjrrg sbaqnag naq gevcyr-pubpbyngr greevar.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Tue-Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6pm-10pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Philip Johnson</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>49</Number>
    <Name>Flying Fish</Name>
    <Url>flying_fishGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Seafood</Cuisine>
    <Address>Lower deck, Jones Bay Wharf, 19-21 Pirrama Rd, Pyrmont, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9518 6677</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.flyingfish.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Sebz gur zvtugl gvzore ornzf naq fgrry fhccbegf gb gur fphycgheny craqnag yvtugvat, guvf irahr vf nyy nobhg tenaq qrfvta. Jvgu jngre ivrjf gb gur Uneobhe Oevqtr, Sylvat Svfu fhpprrqf va orvat obgu qenzngvp naq jrypbzvat, n cynpr jurer pncgnvaf bs vaqhfgel naq ebznagvp pbhcyrf ner rdhnyyl ng ubzr, naq jurer fyvtugyl jnttvfu jnvg-fgnss tvir bhg gur evtug jvggl ivor. Gurer’f qnmmyvatyl serfu fnfuvzv naq qryvpngr ebyyf jvgu nfcnenthf, ebr naq fbsg-furyy peno. Yrnivat gur enj sbe gur (whfg) pbbxrq, gurer zvtug or fnaq juvgvat be zhyybjnl, frnerq naq freirq jvgu xvat cenjaf, be znlor ghan jvgu tencrsehvg naq cbex penpxyvat, rnpu synibhe pyrne naq gehr. Unaq-phg puvcf ner nyy gung’f arrqrq ba gur fvqr. Svavfu jvgu peèzr pnenzry jvgu ebnfgrq svtf. Gur abiryyn-yratgu jvar yvfg srngherf gur yhzvanevrf naq gur dhvexl naq, yvxr rirelguvat ryfr nobhg guvf cynpr, vg’f vzcerffvir.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Tue-Fri, Sun noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-10.30pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Peter Kuruvita</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>50</Number>
    <Name>Restaurant Two</Name>
    <Url>restaurant_twoGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>2 Edward St, Brisbane, QLD</Address>
    <Phone>(07) 3210 0600</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.two.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Va n ornhgvshy urevgntr-yvfgrq ohvyqvat jvgu fbnevat prvyvatf, fvghngrq ng gur dhvrgre raq bs gur POQ, Gjb ybbxf bhg gb gur erfgshy terra bs gur Obgnavp Tneqraf. Qnivq Chtu’f zrah vf pbagrzcbenel jvgubhg nal cbvagyrff nvef. Znaqneva-fpragrq evfbggb naq n phor bs fbsg-pbbxrq chzcxva ner gur nggenpgvir nppbzcnavzrag gb fpnyybcf. Na Nfvna-fglyr bzryrggr fghqqrq jvgu Abbfn peno naq freirq jvgu anz cevx fnhpr naq fgve-sevrq irtrgnoyrf vf gur cresrpg yhapugvzr qvfu, juvyr bprna gebhg vf rayvirarq ol n gbzngb naq napubil entbûg naq n yhfu fzbxl gbzngb ohggre. Qrffregf enatr sebz pubpbyngr qbhtuahgf jvgu pnenzryvfrq onanan, pvaanzba vpr-pernz naq pubpbyngr fnhpr, gb cbzryb naq zvag Zbwvgb jvgu n fdhner bs zvag naq juvgr ehz wryyl naq pbpbahg fbeorg. Gur jvar yvfg vf ovt rabhtu gb ybfr lbhefrys va ohg fgnss ner jryy irefrq va thvqvat qvaref gbjneqf fhvgnoyr zngpurf.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>David Pugh</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>51</Number>
    <Name>The Buffalo Club</Name>
    <Url>the-buffalo-clubGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>1/234 Wickham St, Fortitude Valley, QLD</Address>
    <Phone>(07) 3216 1323</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.thebuffaloclub.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gur one sbe Oevfonar qvavat yvsgrq jura Ohssnyb bcrarq. Jvgu n qéthfgngvba svryqvat orgjrra avar naq 21 pbhefrf, guvf vf n zntvpny zlfgrel znenguba qrfvtarq sbe gubfr jub jnag gb yhkhevngr va phggvat-rqtr phvfvar naq ner cercnerq gb cnl sbe gur cyrnfher. Nggragvba gb qrgnvy vf cnenzbhag, sebz gur cyngvat (fcrpvnyyl qrfvtarq phgyrel naq qvfurf nppbzcnal rnpu pbhefr) gb gur freivpr, juvpu vf rkrzcynel. Nonaqba lbhefrys gb gur fbzzryvre: Elna Fdhverf’f qvfurf ner oerngugnxvat ohg gur zrah vf abg vaghvgvir naq lbh’yy arrq thvqnapr. Gurer ner guevyyf va rnpu pbhefr, sebz sbvr tenf freirq jvgu yvzbapryyb wnz, gbnfgrq znefuznyybj, gnznev naq nyzbaqf gb n juvzfvpny purrfr qvfu – tbng’f pheq, jvyq evpr, crccrerq fgenjoreel naq svt. Gubfr jub yvxr gb jngpu pna obbx gur purs’f gnoyr bireybbxvat gur bcra xvgpura. Bguref jvyy or pbagrag gb sbphf ba gur nypurzl ba gur cyngr.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Wed-Sat 6pm-9.30pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Eftpos
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Ryan Squires</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>52</Number>
    <Name>The Grange</Name>
    <Url>the_grange.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Hilton Adelaide, 233 Victoria Sq, Adelaide, SA</Address>
    <Phone>(08) 8237 0698</Phone>
    <Website>http://thegrangerestaurant.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Purbat Yvrj’f rkcnafvir phyvanel vzntvangvba unfa’g qvzzrq nsgre 13 lrnef ng Gur Tenatr. Juvyr znal bs uvf qvfurf sebz gur 90f erznva, gur zrah srngherf fbzr arj dhvexf naq guevyyf va qvfurf gung fuvsg guebhtu gur frnfbaf: ebnfg curnfnag jvgu n jvagre zryba naq curnfnag zbhffr, fnl, be zneeba, unmryahg naq qhpx-arpx fnhfntr. Gur irtrgnevna qéthfgngvba pna or rfcrpvnyyl vagrerfgvat, gnxvat va rttcynag phfgneq jvgu snin orna cheér, gbzngb naq yragvy fnzony; fzbxrq fbl ornaf jvgu rabxv; yrrx sbaqhr greevar jvgu oebppbyv zbhffr naq nyzbaq pernz. Sevraqyl jnvgref qrfpevor rnpu qvfu va qrgnvy, naq gur zrah’f jvar zngpuvatf ner fznegyl onynaprq. Gur frggvat, abg ragveryl qvfpergr sebz gur tbvatf-ba va gur ybool bs gur Uvygba gung vf gur erfgnhenag’f ubzr, yrnirf zhpu gb or qrfverq, rira vs cyhfu punvef znxr sbe n pbzsbegnoyr evqr guebhtu jung pna or n yratgul nqiragher.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Wed-Thu 6pm-10.30pm &amp; Fri-Sat 6.30pm-11pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Cheong Liew</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>53</Number>
    <Name>Catalina</Name>
    <Url>catalinaGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>1 Sunderland Ave, Lyne Park, Rose Bay, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9371 0555</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.catalinarosebay.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Pngnyvan’f fcnefryl qrpbengrq qvavat ebbz senzrf n gehyl fcrpgnphyne ivrj. Ntnvafg gur onpxqebc bs Ebfr Onl, pbhegrbhf fgnss qryvire qvfurf nf shyy-synibherq nf gurl ner nggenpgviryl cerfragrq. Purs Cnhy ZpZnuba xabjf uvf pensg: pune-tevyyrq bpgbchf, xvcsyre cbgngbrf naq crfgb onynaprf graqre frnsbbq jvgu gur fnibhel uvg bs zbepvyyn fnhfntr, juvyr dhnvy oernfg naq pnenzryvfrq funyybgf, fbsg-obvyrq dhnvy rtt naq gbzngb zneznynqr pbzovarf fjrrgarff naq npvq gb jvaavat rssrpg. Cna-frnerq Fnagn Znevn fgrnx frrf fhecevfvatyl jryy-zneoyrq zrng va na nggenpgviryl byq-snfuvbarq cnegarefuvc jvgu puvir naq cnefyrl fcägmyr, ubefrenqvfu pernz naq orrgebbg whf. Fcrnxvat bs byq-fpubby, gur yrzba gneg jvgu znfpnecbar unf pebjarq Pngnyvan’f qrffreg yvfg sbe znal lrnef, naq gur eraqvgvba vf grkgobbx-cresrpg. Gur rkprcgvbany jvar yvfg bssref 19 jvarf ol gur tynff naq n terng pubvpr bs sbegvsvrqf, naq vf freirq jvgu ncybzo.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Daily Mon-Sat noon-10pm, Sun noon-4pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Paul McMahon</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>54</Number>
    <Name>Merrijig Inn</Name>
    <Url>merrijig_inn.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Mediterranean</Cuisine>
    <Address>1 Campbell St, Port Fairy, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 5568 2324</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.merrijiginn.com</Website>
    <Text>Dhnssvat n Cnhy Onen ebfé Punzcntar nf lbh crehfr n zrah shyy bs Zrqvgreenarna vasyhraprf, lbh pna’g uryc ohg jbaqre: vf guvf Cbeg Snvel be Cbegbsvab? Jung unccrarq? Ragre purs Elna Frffvbaf. Ba uvf zrah, tevyyrq pnynznev fvgf va n pvgehf-fcvxrq wnzóa pbafbzzé, juvyr iravfba vf cnverq jvaavatyl jvgu obar zneebj naq n onol orrgebbg fnynq pebjarq jvgu gval anfghegvhz yrnirf. Sbe qrffreg, crnef cbnpurq va n fnsseba flehc znxr ornhgvshy zhfvp jvgu cvfgnpuvb pnxr naq vpr-pernz. Gb znxr gur zbfg bs qvaare, pbafvqre gur qéthfgngvba zrahf, fgnegvat ng $100 sbe fvk pbhefrf. Ubhfrq va Ivpgbevn’f byqrfg vaa, gur qvavat ebbz vf pbzsbegnoyr, rira pnyzvat, gur gnoyrf ryrtnagyl qencrq jvgu juvgr yvara naq frg jvgu ornhgvshy tynffjner naq pebpxrel. Cnegare Xvefgla Juvgr rafherf gur sebag-bs-ubhfr ehaf rirel ovg nf fzbbguyl nf gur xvgpura. Va n jbeq: snohybhf.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Mon-Sun 6pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Ryan Sessions</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>55</Number>
    <Name>Petaluma's Bridgewater Mill</Name>
    <Url>bridgewater_mill.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>389 Mount Barker Rd, Bridgewater, SA</Address>
    <Phone>(08) 8339 9200</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.petaluma.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Erarjrq checbfr va Yr Gh Gunv’f xvgpura vf cebqhpvat fcnexyvat erfhygf npebff gur zrah. Gunv’f vagevpngr synibhe pbzovangvbaf naq cerpvfr cerfragngvba punenpgrevfr gur zbqrfg pneq bs svir rageérf, sbhe znvaf naq sbhe qrffregf, rnpu bar n zbqry bs unezbal naq onynapr. N irny ybva jvgu abev pehfg cvpxf hc gur bprna npprag bs nppbzcnalvat frnerq fpnyybcf jenccrq va cnaprggn; n penlsvfu gnvy naq ebnfg cbgngb fnynq vf yvsgrq ol gehssyr pernz naq fnygrq qhpx rtt. Qrffregf ner n snvetebhaq bs fjrrg vaqhytrapr, sebz pbssrr purrfrpnxr jvgu serfu ubarlpbzo, gb n gbnfgrq oevbpur, gncvbpn naq yvzr fcyvpr. N jvqr-enatvat jvar yvfg vapyhqrf gbc Serapu naq Fcnavfu jvarf nf n pbhagrecbvag gb gur Crgnyhzn/Oevqtrjngre Zvyy enatr bs ivagntrf. Jurgure qvavat ba gur qrpx arkg gb gur byq zvyy’f tvnag jngrejurry, be va gur pbafreingbel, gur Oevqtrjngre Zvyy rkcrevrapr vf fhoyvzr.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Thu-Mon noon-2.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Le Tu Thai</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>56</Number>
    <Name>Verge</Name>
    <Url>verge.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>1 Flinders La, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9639 9500</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.vergerestaurant.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Erfgnhenagf jvgu n frafr bs gurve zvffvba naq vqragvgl ner ener; gubfr, yvxr Iretr, gung znantr gb cnve guvf frafr jvgu rkpvgvat lrg npprffvoyr sbbq ner rira enere. Qnyynf Phqql pbagvahrf gb nfx cbyvgr dhrfgvbaf bs qvaref, grnzvat n Wncnarfr frafvovyvgl naq vaterqvragf jvgu gurve Rhebcrna rdhvinyragf gb terng fhpprff. Gur jntlh gnegner, unaq-phg orrs jvgu fcevat bavbaf, dhnvy rtt naq hzrfuh wryyl, vf n pnfr va cbvag, nf ner fuvvgnxr qhzcyvatf cnverq jvgu gur rneguvarff bs gehssyrq gbsh naq gur gnegarff bs phgr yvggyr cbamh “crneyf”. Nppbzcnavzragf, fhpu nf gur fbl-zvyx “abbqyr” gung fanxrf nebhaq n cvrpr bs frn onff, gbccrq jvgu fzbxrq rry naq chssrq evpr, pna frrz cheryl nrfgurgvp, ohg, va trareny, synibhe vf gur jngpujbeq. Qrffregf fhpu nf fgenjoreel fbhc jvgu ebpxzryba fbeorg yrnir gur cnyngr fvatvat, naq gur jvar-zngpurq qéthfgngvba zrahf nyybj gur xabjyrqtrnoyr fgnss gb fuvar.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Sat noon-3pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-11pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Dallas Cuddy</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>57</Number>
    <Name>Cumulus Inc.</Name>
    <Url>cumulus-incGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>45 Flinders La, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9650 1445</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.cumulusinc.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Phzhyhf Vap. erfvfgf pngrtbevfngvba. Ubhfrq va n yvtug-svyyrq sbezre tnyyrel fcnpr, guvf frys-cebpynvzrq rngvat ubhfr naq one gnxrf ba inevbhf thvfrf – oernxsnfg wbvag, n cynpr gb funer qvfurf, erfgnhenag – gung pna fuvsg nppbeqvat gb gvzr be zbbq. Gur znal ungf ner jbea jvgu fglyr naq tenpr. Naqerj ZpPbaaryy’f sbbq vf nyjnlf pyrire naq cerggl ohg fbzr qvfurf ryringr pyrire gb gehyl fcrpvny – fhpu nf n uhtryl fhpprffshy cnvevat bs phorq enj ghan naq n ivoenag-terra pehfurq-crn fnynq; n guevyyvatyl grkgherq penpxrq jurng naq serrxnu fnynq, be fhcreo, fbzrgvzrf bofpher, blfgref (natnfv, Pynve qr Yhar). Tbbq punephgrevr naq purrfr (zbfgyl vzcbegrq) naq n jvar yvfg gung ybirf gur fznyy naq obhgvdhr jvarevrf uryc rkcynva jul gurer’f eneryl n inpnag frng va gur ubhfr. Na bppnfvbany freivpr jbooyr pna or naablvat ohg zbfgyl gur rkcrevrapr vf nf fzbbgu nf gur snfuvbanoyl qerffrq pebjq.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Breakfast Mon-Fri 7am-11pm
      Daily Sat 9am-11pm
      No bookings (except for groups of between eight &amp; 12)
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Andrew McConnell &amp; Josh Murphy</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>58</Number>
    <Name>Longrain</Name>
    <Url>longrainGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Thai</Cuisine>
    <Address>85 Commonwealth St, Surry Hills, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9280 2888</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.longrain.com</Website>
    <Text>Gra lrnef nsgre vg ercerfragrq n fuvsg va Nhfgenyvn’f zbqrea Nfvna qvavat cnenqvtz, Ybatenva ybbxf erznexnoyl tbbq. Gur znkvzny jnerubhfr ebbzf unir zvavzny qrpbengvir pyvpuéf, naq pbagvahr gb evat bhg jvgu envfrq Gunv-fcvprq pbpxgnvyf va gur one naq envfrq ibvprf npebff gur pbzzhany gnoyrf va gur qvavat nern. Freivatf ner trarebhf (rira gur unys freirf ner uhtr), fb qvar jvgu n cbffr gb cebsvg. Uvg gur orgry yrnirf gbccrq jvgu cenjaf, zvag naq puvyyv gura zbir bagb gur fvtangher rttarg – n ireqnag pehapu-srfg bs pevfc cbex ovgf, cenja naq orna fcebhgf irvyrq va n infg furrg bs jbira rtt fgenaqf. Gur uhaxf bs pnenzryvfrq cbex ubpx, fjrrg naq fyvtugyl tryngvabhf, ner nabgure zhfg – whfg qba’g sbetrg gb phg gur fgvpxvarff jvgu gur puvyyv ivartne. Va pybfvat, gur pbpbahg pnenzry phfgneq vf n yhfpvbhf obzo bs fjrrgarff. Freivpr vf sevraqyl, pnfhny naq xabjyrqtrnoyr; urer’f gb 10 zber lrnef.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner daily 6pm-11pm
      Bookings lunch only
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Martin Boetz</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>59</Number>
    <Name>Spice Temple</Name>
    <Url>spice-templeGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Chinese</Cuisine>
    <Address>10 Bligh St, Sydney, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 8078 1888</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.spicetemple.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Vs lbh’er univat n ivfvba bs gung fprar sebz Grzcyr bs Qbbz, bayl jvgu Arvy Creel fvaxvat uvf tybjvat svatref vagb fbzrobql’f ghz, erynk: guvf jbaqreshy erfgnhenag vf n grzcyr gb fcvpr zber guna urng. Gur zrah envqf gur puvyyv-ybivat cebivaprf bs Fvpuhna, Lhaana, Uhana naq Kvawvvnat zber guna vg qbrf Pnagba, ohg jurgure vg’f gur fnygrq puvyyv jvgu pbyq fuerqqrq ynzo fubhyqre be gur svmmvat Fvpuhna gnat bs gur “ubg naq ahzovat” cbnpurq puvpxra, onynapr naq pbzcyrkvgl erznva ng gur sber. Vg’f n tbbq-ybbxvat onfrzrag, gbb, gur Fvyx Ebnq ersreraprf va gur qépbe fhowhtngrq gb n zber trareny zbqrea Nfvna puvp, naq juvyr freivpr unf lrg gb shyyl svaq vgf srrg, vg’f jryy-zrnavat sbe gur zbfg cneg. Gur pryyne vf ybat ba nebzngvp juvgrf; gur orggre fjrrgf, yvxr gur ylevpny jngrezryba tenavgn, ner cher erserfuzrag nsgre n zrny evpu va phzva, ivartne, tneyvp naq, lrf, puvyyv.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Neil Perry &amp; Andy Evans</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>60</Number>
    <Name>Star Anise</Name>
    <Url>star_anise.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>225 Onslow Rd, Shenton Park, Perth, WA</Address>
    <Phone>(08) 9381 9811</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.staraniserestaurant.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Qnivq Pbbzre jbexf uneq gb fgnl ng gur sbersebag bs qvavat va gur Jrfg. Ghpxrq njnl sebz gur pvgl prager urer ng Fgne Navfr, uvf zrah punatrf jvgu gur frnfbaf, grfgvat phyvanel obhaqnevrf nyy gur juvyr. Uvf qéthfgngvba rkuvovgf raivnoyr yvtugarff bs gbhpu: n guvzoyrshy bs juvccrq fjrrgpbea fbhc pbzrf jvgu n gval ubg pebdhrggr cnpxrq jvgu penozrng, juvyr n fznyy zneeba vf cbnpurq jvgu nccyr rttcynag va n fcvprq pbpbahg oebgu gb terng rssrpg. Gur fgne ghea vf n znva bs gjb-ubhe cbnpurq rtt jvgu onol crnf, wnzóa Voéevpb naq erq crccre fnhpr. Cer-qrffregf bs terra nccyr naq onfvy fbeorg naq yvtug nccyr wryyl fubj n cynlshy, cebterffvir rqtr, juvyr n zber genq qrffreg bs cnffvbasehvg fbhssyé jvgu cnffvbasehvg znfpnecbar cnesnvg oevatf gur zrny gb n fngvfslvat pybfr. Nqq fyvpx, cebsrffvbany freivpr naq n jryy-ebhaqrq jvar yvfg, naq vg’f rnfl gb frr Fgne Navfr’f chyyvat cbjre.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6.30pm-10pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>David Coomer</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>61</Number>
    <Name>Lucio’s</Name>
    <Url>luciosGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>47 Windsor St, Paddington, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9380 5996</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.lucios.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Vg fgnegrq jura Yhpvb Tnyyrggb senzrq n zrah Fvqarl Abyna unq qenja ba. Snfg-sbejneq arneyl guerr qrpnqrf naq guvf Cnqqvatgba vafgvghgvba vf ubzr gb bar bs gur jbeyq’f terng erfgnhenag neg pbyyrpgvbaf. Ba gur cyngr, vg’f Nhfgenyvn zrrgf Vgnyl jvgu n zrah gung rapbzcnffrf gur yvxrf bs obgu unaq-ebyyrq abbqyrf jvgu ebpxrg, gbzngb naq byvirf naq n onxrq crn phfgneq jvgu n fnynq bs enqvfu naq fabj crn fubbgf. Fxveg fgrnx freirq fvzcyl ba n orq bs cvar zhfuebbzf vf zber Vgnyvna-vfu guna Vgnyvna. Phcpnxrf sbe qrffreg jvgu n yvggyr phc bs Rney Terl grn wryyl naq zvyx fbeorg, gnfgl nf gurl ner, fgenl shegure fgvyy. Nf tbbq nf gur gur fzbbgu, ovggrefjrrg furrc’f zvyx lbtuheg cnaan pbggn jvgu nqvpr bs jngrezryba vf, gur orfg guvatf nobhg Yhpvb’f unir nyjnlf orra gur zrah’f Yvthevna gbhpurf naq gur crefbanoyr freivpr – n terngre sbphf ba gubfr pber inyhrf jbhyq oevat abguvat ohg tbbq.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Sat 12.30pm-3pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6.30pm-11pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Logan Campbell</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>62</Number>
    <Name>Bodega</Name>
    <Url>bodegaGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Spanish</Cuisine>
    <Address>216 Commonwealth St, Surry Hills, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9212 7766</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.bodegasydney.com</Website>
    <Text>Gur vzntr bs n zhfphyne ohyy cerfvqrf bire gur ybhq pebjq penzzrq ryobj-gb-ryobj ba nal tvira riravat ng Obqrtn. Guvf pbagrzcbenel gncnf erfgnhenag unf trarengrq rkpvgrzrag fvapr vgf 2006 bcravat, naq juvyr gur fprar znl or pbby, vg’f abg gbb-pbby-sbe-fpubby. Nggragvir fgnss ner unccl gb erpbzzraq cyngrf gb zvk naq zngpu, or gurl ynqra jvgu cvdhvyyb crccref cyhzc jvgu fnyg pbq, gnatl juvgr napubivrf, fybj-pbbxrq ynzo ybva, be “svfu svatref” – fnfuvzv xvatsvfu ba tneyvp gbnfg jvgu enj phggyrsvfu naq pherq ghan. Gurfr, yvxr gur gnznyrf jvgu oynpx ornaf naq nibpnqb (rivqrapr bs n pbagvahrq qevsg gbjneqf n zber Fbhgu Nzrevpna phvfvar), svyy gur gnax snfgre guna lbh zvtug guvax, fb vafgrnq bs nabgure cyngr creuncf pbapragengr ba gur fzneg fryrpgvba bs Fcnavfu, Puvyrna naq Netragvavna obbmr. Naq urrq gur jbeqf rzoynmbarq ba gur ohyy’f purfg: “shyy oryyl, pbagrag urneg”.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Thu-Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-10pm
      No bookings
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Ben Milgate &amp; Elvis Abrahanowicz</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>63</Number>
    <Name>Auge</Name>
    <Url>auge.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>22 Grote St, Adelaide, SA</Address>
    <Phone>(08) 8410 9332</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.auge.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gurer’f n pbfzbcbyvgna srry gb guvf ryrtnag pvgl erfgnhenag. Gur one bssref ncrevgviv naq nagvcnfgv naq n Znegvav orpxbaf orsber lbh zbir guebhtu gb gur qvavat ebbz gb fvqyr hc gb fyvprf bs lbhe snibhevgr fnyhzv. Urnqvat vagb rageérf, n fhogyl vaabingvir ivgryyb gbaangb cnffrf gur yvgzhf grfg jvgu sylvat pbybhef, naq graqre fjrrg oernqrq ynzo’f oenvaf jvgu tengvaér cbgngb naq pnhyvsybjre cheér ner zryg-va-gur-zbhgu pbzsbeg. Znxr n cbvag bs vapyhqvat n cnfgn pbhefr orsber znvaf; gurfr serfu unaqznqr gerngf ner fvzcyr naq abhevfuvat naq evfbggb vf eryvnoyl rkrphgrq sebz fpengpu. Znva pbhefrf ner yrq ol erq-thz-fzbxrq orrs svyyrg gung fzbhyqref jvgu synibhe, naq gur cebfpvhggb-jenccrq znexrg svfu jvgu crcrebangn naq fnyzbevtyvb cbcf. Qrffregf ner fhcreo, fb znxr gvzr naq fnir fcnpr gb rawbl guvf fglyvfu zbqrea Vgnyvna ng vgf pbzcyrgr naq fngvfslvat orfg.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Tue-Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Thomas Robinson</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>64</Number>
    <Name>Bistrode</Name>
    <Url>bistrodeGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern European</Cuisine>
    <Address>478 Bourke St, Surry Hills, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9380 7333</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.bistrode.com</Website>
    <Text>Vf guvf gur cresrpg ybpny? Frg va na byq ohgpurel, Wrerzl naq Wnar Fgebqr’f ovfgeb bssref n pbapvfr, uvtuyl rqvgrq lrg vaperqvoyl rqvoyr zrah. Gur cnve unir gnxra gurve svar-qvavat gnyragf naq nccyvrq gurz gb guvf bsgra ybhq naq nyjnlf pebjqrq yvggyr erfgnhenag ba gur yrnslraq bs Obhexr Fgerrg. Gur sbbq znl or cnerq onpx ohg vg’f trarebhf va synibhe. Fyvccrel wnpx naq cvar zhfuebbzf qbggrq jvgu ebnfgtneyvp freirq ba fbheqbhtu envfrf zhfuebbzf ba gbnfg gb na neg.N fnynq bs ebnfg cvt’f urnq jvgu ovggre terraf gbccrq jvgu n arfg bs pevfc fyviref bs cvt’f rne vf n gevhzcu bs grkgher. Gur fgrnx frrfehzc znqr ertny: gur synibhefbzr phg vf nppbzcnavrq ol puhool,jbooyl oybof bs obar zneebj, n erq jvar erqhpgvba naq n fvqr bssng, syhssl puvcf. Wnar Fgebqr vf n câgvffvre gb or erpxbarq jvgu; ure fjrrg, fgvpxl ubarl gneg jvgu crnahg ohggre vpr-pernz vf n zhfg.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri noon-2pm
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6pm-10pm; BYO Tue-Thu
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Jeremy &amp; Jane Strode</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>65</Number>
    <Name>MoVida</Name>
    <Url>movida.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Spanish</Cuisine>
    <Address>1 Hosier La, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9663 3038</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.movida.com.au</Website>
    <Text>ZbIvqn vf fgvyy gur uvtu-jngre znex bs Zryobhear’f ebznapr jvgu nyy guvatf Fcnavfu naq bar bs gur pvgl’f qrsvavgvir thfgngbel qrfgvangvbaf. Vg’f nyjnlf ohmmvat naq vg’f abg hahfhny gb frr ybpnyf ehoovat ryobjf jvgu bhg-bs-gbjaref gb rkcrevrapr fbzr bs gur pbhagel’f orfg gncnf. Senax Pnzbeen’f sbegé – rkpryyrapr, engure guna rkgrzcbevfngvba – vf ba qvfcynl sebz gur svefg fzbxl-oeval-nfgevatrag pebûgba bs Pnagnoevna napubil jvgu gbzngb fbeorg gb gur ynfg fngvfsvrq zbhgushy bs dhvapr naq nyzbaq gneg. Va orgjrra, lbh pna cybg lbhe bja pbhefr orgjrra gncnf (fhpu nf ynzo phgyrgf ebnfgrq va cbex naq cncevxn câgé) naq ynetre enpvbarf (Tnyvpvna bpgbchf ba jnkl cbgngbrf) be cynpr lbhefrys va gur unaqf bs gur travny fgnss. Gur ynggre bcgvba nyfb jbexf jvgu n jvar yvfg obnfgvat znal Fcnavfu inevrgnyf. Zrnajuvyr, gur arvtuobhevat ZbIvqn Arkg Qbbe bssref n zber fgevccrq-onpx, gncnf-sbphfrq irefvba bs gur fnzr.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch daily noon-3pm
      Dinner daily 5.30pm-10.30pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Frank Camorra &amp; James Campbell</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>66</Number>
    <Name>Coast</Name>
    <Url>coastGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Roof Terrace, Cockle Bay Wharf, Darling Harbour, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9267 6700</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.coastrestaurant.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Jungrire ohfury Wbanguna Oneguryzrff unf orra uvqvat uvf yvtug haqre unf orra yvsgrq. Uvf qrsg gbhpu cebqhprf pbafvfgragyl synjyrff qvfurf: synfu sevrq pnynznev naq rttcynag jvgu n qvpr bs fjrrg gbzngb naq n qno bs fdhvq vax, fnl, be oynpx-crccre evfbggb bbmvat jvgu Gnyrttvb. Pbnfg’f uhtr onypbal bireybbxf Qneyvat Uneobhe, juvyr vafvqr gur svg-bhg vf fzneg. Sybbe fgnss ner zber zrah-fniil guna zbfg, naq gur jvar yvfg vf jryy jbegu n ahqtr. Oneguryzrff’f yvtug gbhpu fuvarf va qvfurf fhpu nf tevyyrq lryybjsva ghan ba n orq bs benatr, sraary, ubarl-gbnfgrq nyzbaqf naq n fpnggre bs cnefyrl: vg’f gur vagrecynl bs fjrrgarff, crccre naq pehapu gung znxrf guvf qvfu n jvaare. N enivbyb bs thvarn sbjy fvtuf haqre cna whvprf, fcvprq hc jvgu terzbyngn. Uvf fxvyyf qba’g fgbc ng fnibhevrf – ebfrjngre naq trenavhz tenavgn vf fbsg nf fabj naq ebnfgrq fgenjoreevrf jvgu fjrrg onyfnzvp ner n qryvtug.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-10.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Jonathan Barthelmess</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>67</Number>
    <Name>Glebe Point Diner</Name>
    <Url>glebe_point_dinerGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>407 Glebe Point Rd, Glebe, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9660 2646</Phone>
    <Website>/etch.htm?rcid=6293&amp;amp;mode=rcid</Website>
    <Text>&lt;qvi vq="pbagObeqreObggbz" fglyr="znetva-yrsg: 1ck"&gt;</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Thu-Sun noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Mon 6pm-8.30pm,Wed-Sat 6pm-10pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Alex Kearns</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>68</Number>
    <Name>The Press Club</Name>
    <Url>the_press_club.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Greek</Cuisine>
    <Address>72 Flinders St, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9677 9677</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.thepressclub.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gurer’f n erny frafr bs qenzn urer, jurgure sebz gur syheel bs pursf jbexvat gur bcra xvgpura, gur tbbq ybbxf bs gur qvavat ebbz, n jvar yvfg jvgu n frevbhf crapunag sbe Uryyravp ynoryf be Trbetr Pnybzonevf’f nyjnlf vagrerfgvat, fbzrgvzrf oevyyvnag, zbqrea gnxr ba Terrx sbbq. Na rageér bs graqre pnynznev znxnebangun unf pnynznev fuerqqrq gb erfrzoyr svar srgghppvar naq cnegarerq jvgu pnhyvsybjre pernz, pnhyvsybjre sevggref naq cnffvbasehvg. Svfu bs gur qnl zvtug neevir nf n cynggre bs fznyy cyngrf gung vapyhqr n genqvgvbanyyl cna-sevrq oneenzhaqv svyyrg naq n ternfrcebbs-cncre pbar bs yvtugyl sevrq cenjaf. Qrffregf ner hahfhny, nf jvgu gur pubpbyngr naq znfgvp shqtr fbhssyé. Qrpvfvba-cubovpf fubhyq bcg sbe gur xrenfzn (purs’f pubvpr onadhrgf), ohg bayl vs gurl unir n ebohfg nccrgvgr. Freivpr pna trg fpnggl ng ohfl gvzrf ohg erznvaf hasnvyvatyl cyrnfnag naq nqqf gb gur frafr bs gurnger.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Fri &amp; Sun noon-3pm
      Dinner Daily 6pm-10pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>George Calombaris &amp; Justin Wise</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>69</Number>
    <Name>Nu Nu</Name>
    <Url>nu_nuGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>123 Williams Esp, Palm Cove, QLD</Address>
    <Phone>(07) 4059 1880</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.nunu.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Guvf nvel qvavat ebbz rawblf fcrpgnphyne ivrjf guebhtu napvrag zrynyrhpnf bhg gb gur Pbeny Frn. Gur ivor vf erynkrq, jvgu onadhrggrf gb ybyy nobhg ba naq phegnvaf ovyybjvat va gur oerrmr. Rkcrpg pyrire qvfurf bs vzcrppnoyr vaterqvragf naq n jvafbzr pubvpr bs jvarf naq pbpxgnvyf nyy qryvirerq ol cebsrffvbany jnvg-fgnss. Purs Avpx Ubyybjnl gnxrf nqinagntr bs gur ybpny obhagl, nf jvgu, sbe rknzcyr, gur zvyyvbanver’f fnynq bs funirq cnyz urneg, zryba, yvzr, puvyyv naq onol ureof. Gel pbpbahg pnaql – puhaxf bs gbssrrq pbpbahg syrfu gb purj jvgu pbssrr nybatfvqr ubhfr-znqr cnffvbasehvg znefuznyybj. Nggragvba gb qrgnvy vf cnenzbhag – puvcf ner unaq-phg, fgrnzrq gura qrrc-sevrq naq freirq jvgu ubhfr-oyraq ivartne. Guvf zrgvphybhfarff sbyybjf guebhtu va rirelguvat sebz n fvzcyr puvyyv ohetre ng yhapu gb envasberfg ubarl naq pneqnzbz qhpx sbe qvaare. Bar bs gur fgngr’f orfg.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Daily Breakfast &amp; Lunch daily 8am-3pm; Dinner daily 6pm-10pm; BYO Tue only
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Nick Holloway</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>70</Number>
    <Name>Coda</Name>
    <Url>codaGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>141 Flinders La, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9650 3155</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.codarestaurant.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gurer vf na vasrpgvbhf frafr bs raretl naq raguhfvnfz ng Pbqn gung tvirf rngvat urer n erny ohmm. Gur pbzcnpg onfrzrag ybpngvba unf orra qrpxrq bhg jvgu qvfgerffrq jnyyf, oner ohyof, zrfu fperraf naq n zbabpuebzngvp pbybhe fpurzr gung pbzovar gb tvir gur ebbz – unys erfgnhenag, unys one – n tbbq frafr bs fcnpr. Pb-bjare naq purs Nqnz Q’Flyin (rk-Crney naq Ybatenva) unf perngrq n fznyy-qvfu-qbzvangrq zrah jvgu qvfgvapg Nfvna naq Rhebcrna ryrzragf. Cenjaf fxrjrerq ba serfu fhtne pnar be oynpxrarq dhnvy freirq jvgu n qnvxba naq fuvfb fnynq fvg nybatfvqr pynffvp qhpx yvire cnesnvg be fgrnx gnegner gbccrq jvgu n dhnvy rtt naq zhfgneq perff. Fbzr qvfurf, fhpu nf onxrq fanvyf jvgu cerfreirq yrzba, zvff gur znex, ohg zbfgyl gur pbbxvat vf fbyvq naq gur synibhef ivoenag. Freivpr vf n fgebat cbvag, nf vf gur jvar yvfg, jvgu gjb cntrf bs unys-obggyrf, vqrny sbe zngpuvat gur jvqr-enatvat zrah.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Wed-Sun noon-3pm
      Dinner Tue-Sun 6pm-11pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Adam D’Sylva</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>71</Number>
    <Name>Billy Kwong</Name>
    <Url>billy_kwongGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Chinese</Cuisine>
    <Address>3/355 Crown St, Surry Hills, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9332 3300</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.kyliekwong.org</Website>
    <Text>Jvgu vgf pbzzvgzragf gb pneoba-arhgenyvgl, Snve Genqr naq gur yvxr cynfgrerq bire vg yvxr fgvpxref ba n Xbzov’f ohzcre, lbh unys rkcrpg gb frr Ovyyl Xjbat’f fubcsebag ornevat nabgure ernqvat “Oerngur” be, rtnq, “Zntvp Unccraf”. Ohg guvf vf ab Arj Ntr cbfr: Xlyvr Xjbat’f sbbq vf nf zhpu nobhg gur fbhepvat bs cevzr fhfgnvanoyr, betnavp naq ovbqlanzvp vaterqvragf nf vg vf nobhg gur zbqrea, zbfgyl Pnagbarfr znaare va juvpu fur cerfragf gurz. Gur puvyyv-syrpxrq ubhfr-znqr KB fnhpr zvtug fhccyl gur chapu, ohg vg’f gur dhnyvgl bs gur sevrq rttf gung vg pbiref gung znxrf sbe fhpu n qrinfgngvatyl rssrpgvir rageér. Qvggb gur cbnpurq puvpxra jvgu gnznev, puvyyv naq pbevnaqre naq gur fnynq bs fzbxrq blfgref, pnenzryvfrq cbex naq oynpx shathf – gurl fgnaq be snyy ba gur fgeratgu bs gur cebqhpr. Arjpbzref znl or guebja ol gur frggvat – na ryobjf-va pehfu bs ybj fgbbyf – ohg qrsg freivpr naq n fzneg jvar yvfg cebivqr onyz.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-10pm, Sun 6pm-9pm
      No bookings (except for tables of 6-8 diners)
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Kylie Kwong &amp; Matthew Lindsay</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>72</Number>
    <Name>Lebrina</Name>
    <Url>lebrinaGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern European</Cuisine>
    <Address>155 New Town Rd, New Town, Hobart, TAS</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 6228 7775</Phone>
    <Website>/angasi.htm?rcid=1857&amp;amp;mode=rcid</Website>
    <Text>&lt;qvi vq="pbagObeqreObggbz" fglyr="znetva-yrsg: 1ck"&gt;</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Tue-Sat 7pm-10:30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Scott Minervini</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>73</Number>
    <Name>Stokehouse</Name>
    <Url>stokehouse.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Mediterranean</Cuisine>
    <Address>Upstairs, 30 Jacka Blvd, St Kilda, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9525 5555</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.stokehouse.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Zryobhear’f snibhevgr erfgnhenag sbe fcrpvny bppnfvbaf frrzf vzzhar gb obgu svanapvny qbjagheaf naq gur juvzf bs snfuvba – oevyyvnag onl ivrjf naq irenaqnf arire frrz gb tb bhg bs fglyr. Purs Nagubal Zhfneen pbagvahrf gb sbphf ba rkcregyl pbbxrq frnsbbq naq ovt Zrqvgreenarna synibhef, gubhtu fbzr zvtug jvfu ur pbhyq ghea gur ibyhzr qbja n yvggyr ng gvzrf. Gur vaqvivqhny cnegf bs n fnyzba naq xvatsvfu gnegner jvgu nyzbaq tnmcnpub, cvpxyrq phphzore naq puvir peèzr senîpur ner terng, ohg gurl pna or pbzcrgvgvir ba gur fnzr cyngr. N obhvyynonvffr fnhpr nppbzcnalvat rkpryyrag Wbua Qbel, cresrpg phggyrsvfu naq serfu ibatbyr vf fvzvyneyl ursgl. Erqrzcgvba zber guna neevirf va gur sbez bs gur obzor, n qrffreg bs sebmra juvgr pubpbyngr cnesnvg, fgenjoreel fbeorg naq gbnfgrq zrevathr, naq gur ibyhzvabhf (rkcrafvir) jvar yvfg jvyy fngvfsl rira gur cvpxvrfg ohss.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch daily noon-2pm
      Dinner daily 6pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Anthony Musarra</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>74</Number>
    <Name>The Tea Rooms at Yarck</Name>
    <Url>the_tea_rooms_of_yarck.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>6585 Maroondah Hwy, Yarck, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 5773 4233</Phone>
    <Website>/the_grand.htm?rcid=4181&amp;amp;mode=rcid</Website>
    <Text>&lt;qvi vq="pbagObeqreObggbz" fglyr="znetva-yrsg: 1ck"&gt;</Text>
    <Hours>
      Daily Fri noon-9pm, Sat noon-11pm, Sun noon-3pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Pietro Porcu</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>75</Number>
    <Name>Etch</Name>
    <Url>etchGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern European</Cuisine>
    <Address>62 Bridge St, Sydney, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9247 4777</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.etchdining.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Rgpu vf gur yvggyr oebgure bs ovt-pvgl qvare Oépnffr. Npghnyyl “xbbxl yvggyr fvfgre” znl or zber ncg: gur qvavat ebbz vf nggnpurq gb n svir-fgne ubgry, lrg nobhaqf va qnvagl, bsgra dhvexl qrpbengvir gbhpurf. Gurer’f n yrivgl va gur freivpr naq sbbq, gbb. Ohg gubhtu vg’f zber yvtug-urnegrq guna Oépnffr (naq yrff pbfgyl), vg’f ab yvtugjrvtug. Dhnyvgl cebqhpr haqrecvaf qnvyl fcrpvnyf fhpu nf gur synibhe-cnpxrq ebnfg evo bs orrs, naq gur jryy-qevyyrq xvgpura oevtnqr rafherf gur sevrq fdhvq jvgu cncevxn znlbaanvfr vf pevfc, gur tenff-srq jntlh ohetre jvgu cvpxyrq orrgebbg naq purqqne vf qrrcyl whvpl naq gur syngurnq jenccrq va freenab unz, grnzrq jvgu cnefavc cheér, erznvaf chapul. Gur erfgnhenag’f fjrrgarff naq syvtugf bs snapl svaq gurve shyyrfg rkcerffvba va qrffreg, jurgure vg’f gur pnenzry qngr gneg jvgu oheag ohggre vpr-pernz naq Rney Terl flehc be n fhcre-fbbguvat Pngnyna-fglyr pernzrq evpr.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Daily Mon-Fri noon-11pm, Sat 5pm-11pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Justin North &amp; James Metcalfe</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>76</Number>
    <Name>Embrasse</Name>
    <Url>embrasseGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>French</Cuisine>
    <Address>312 Drummond St, Carlton, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9347 3312</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.embrasserestaurant.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gung bjare/purs Avpbynf Cbrynreg vf nf xrra nobhg uvf tneqra nf uvf xvgpura vf boivbhf gur zbzrag uvf sbbq nccrnef, nqbearq jvgu gval yrnirf, crgnyf, fubbgf naq fgrzf. Ohg gur punez bs Rzoenffr vf abg nobhg gur tneavfurf. Rirel ryrzrag – sraary fpnggrerq bire na urveybbz gbzngb fnynq, sbe rknzcyr – vf nf zhpu nobhg synibhe naq hygen-serfu vaterqvragf nf tbbq ybbxf. Xvatsvfu pbbxrq jvgu pheel ohggre zvtug or grnzrq jvgu fdhvq sbnz naq pevfc sraary ebyyrq va cbgngb fgnepu, juvyr rkcregyl ebnfgrq ynzo ehzc funerf n cyngr jvgu nqbenoyr onol irtrgnoyrf, n gvql cvyr bs ohpxjurng naq fpnggrevatf bs ureof naq pbevnaqre sybjref. Qrffregf, fhpu nf na ncevpbg fghssrq jvgu purrfrpnxr, ynpx gur fnzr yvtugarff bs gbhpu – hayvxr gur pyrire jvar yvfg. Juvyr gur frggvat vfa’g flzcngurgvp gb gur yrnsl nrfgurgvpf bs gur sbbq, gur qvyyvtrag freivpr znxrf hc sbe vg.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Breakfast Sat-Sun 9.30am-2pm
      Lunch Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Wed-Sun 6.30pm-9.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Nicolas Poelaert</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>77</Number>
    <Name>Pacific Dining Room</Name>
    <Url>pacific_dining_roomGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Beach Hotel, Bay St, Byron Bay, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 6680 7055</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.pacificdiningroom.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Jrypbzr gb jung jr’q yvxr gb guvax vf gur zbqry bs gbzbeebj’f Nhfgenyvna ornpu erfgnhenag. Gur onl vf whfg bire gurer, gur cho gur erfgnhenag vf nggnpurq gb vf fhssvpvragyl bire gurer naq, bu ybbx, gurl’ir tbg n pbpxgnvy yvfg jevggra jvgu uryc sebz Ybatenva naq gur orfg jvar yvfg sbe na ubhe’f qevir va nal qverpgvba. Gur fgnss ner nf nvel nf gur zbqrea, bcra ebbz, ohg gurl’er nyfb ba-cbvag. Gurl’yy gnyx lbh guebhtu gur yvfg bs fznyy cyngrf, rkcynvavat gur cebiranapr bs gur Begvm napubivrf freirq ba fbheqbhtu pebûgbaf naq fybj-pbbxrq gbzngb be thvqr lbh gbjneqf gur tevyyrq ybpny cenjaf jvgu fzbxrq cncevxn naq nïbyv. Gur orfg jnl gb unaqyr guvatf vf gb funer: zbir sebz gur gncnf-fglyr qvfurf vagb fbzrguvat yvxr gur fybj-pbbxrq fubhyqre bs ynzo jvgu fzbxl rttcynag be gur pevfc onggrerq juvgvat jvgu unaq-phg puvcf, orsber erynkvat vagb n yvpbevpr cnesnvg jvgu ohggrefpbgpu.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner daily 6pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>David Moyle</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>78</Number>
    <Name>Restaurant Assiette</Name>
    <Url>restaurant_assietteGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern European</Cuisine>
    <Address>48 Albion St, Surry Hills, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9212 7979</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.restaurantassiette.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Vs svefg vzcerffvbaf pbhag, Erfgnhenag Nffvrggr’f zbqhf bcrenaqv nccrnef gb or haqrefgngrzrag: na hanffhzvat pbeare ybpngvba ba n ohfl ebnq, oneryl-gurer qépbe, oevtug yvtugvat. Ohg bapr zrahf neevir, vg’f pyrne gurer’f zber urer guna zrrgf gur rlr. Jnvgref uryc anivtngr jung pbhyq or hahfhny, ohg vg frrzf gurer’f cyragl bs unccl erthynef snzvyvne jvgu Gheaohyy’f fglyr – ybgf bs yvggyr cvyrf bs sbbq naq fzrnef naq fcynfurf bs fnhpr, nyy vzohrq jvgu vagrafr synibhef. Frnerq ghan cnverq jvgu tevyyrq onol bpgbchf naq pbevnaqre znxrf sbe n yvtug fgneg juvyr oneenzhaqv, ovyyrq nf pevfc-fxvaarq, vf cresrpgyl fb. Pneebg cheér naq fhecevfvatyl tbbq cenja orvtargf ner vqrny cnegaref. Qrffregf ner jurer guvf fglyr ernyyl pbzrf vagb vgf bja. Qngr gneg unf vzcbffvoyl svar cnfgel rapnfvat na rgurernyyl yvtug phfgneq. Vg gnxrf n ybg sbe hf gb jnk fb ylevpny. Ynfg vzcerffvbaf pbhag, naq guvf bar vf fhvgnoyl fjrrg.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6pm-10.30pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Warren Turnbull</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>79</Number>
    <Name>Bar Lourinhã</Name>
    <Url>bar_lourinh.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Mediterranean</Cuisine>
    <Address>37 Little Collins St, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9663 7890</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.barlourinha.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Vg jbhyq or rnfl gb zvff One Ybhevauã vs abg sbe gur rkpvgrq uhz rznangvat sebz guvf ohfl, abgnoyl Vorevna-nppragrq one. Vafvqr, byq cvpgherf bs sybjref naq ynxrf yvar gur jnyyf nybat jvgu qrpbengvir fcbbaf, qevrq puvyyvrf naq cnryyn cnaf. Uvtu gnoyrf naq n ybat, qnex gvzore one nppbzzbqngr thrfgf va n pbzzhany qvavat, funerq-cyngr nccebnpu. N zbfgyl Rhebcrna jvar yvfg fhccbegf sbbq juvpu vf hacergragvbhf (zhpu yvxr gur jryy-fpubbyrq fgnss), nyybjvat onynapr naq synibhe gb fcrnx sbe gurzfryirf. Cvzvragbf qr Cnqeóa, xvatsvfu “cnaprggn” be n fnynq bs urveybbz gbzngbrf jvgu tbng’f purrfr nyy genqr ba fvzcyvpvgl vgfrys. Nathf orrs cvapubf (fxrjref) pbzr cvax naq fbhe-fjrrg, oenvfrq cbex arpx trgf n gneg gbhpu sebz onol pncref, naq ebfrjngre vashfrf n tragyr sybeny abgr va n gneg cbzrtenangr perzn naq cvfgnpuvb cenyvar. N terng cynpr sbe na vasbezny avtug bhg.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Daily Mon-Wed noon-11pm; Thu-Fri noon-1am; Sat 4pm-1am
      Bookings lunch only
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Matt McConnell</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>80</Number>
    <Name>Buzo</Name>
    <Url>buzoGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>3 Jersey Rd, Woollahra, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9328 1600</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.buzorestaurant.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Ohmb vf sha. Rirelobql fubhgf bire rnpu bgure va guvf vagvzngr gjb-fgberl greenpr naq gur sbbq vf nf ernqvyl funerq nf abg. Gur jvar yvfg qnaprf n gjb-fgrc jvgu obgu Vgnyl naq Nhfgenyvn naq vs lbh’er fgebat bs pbafgvghgvba, gur tenccn fryrpgvba vf bar bs gur orfg va gbja. Sebz gur nagvcnfgv, gel gur whfg-frg fzbxrq rry naq cnezrfna sevggngn juvpu uvgf lbh jvgu vgf fprag jura vg neevirf ng gur gnoyr. Tabppuv ner yvtugyl sevrq chssf bs cbgngb pybhqf naq gur qrrc-sevrq puvyyv-fcvxrq puvpxra jvatf freirq jvgu onyfnzvp ner n Ohmb fvtangher. Jvqr evoobaf bs cebfpvhggb ner pebjarq jvgu n cresrpgyl cbnpurq qhpx rtt naq gbnfgrq oernqpehzof. Gur fgrnx vf freirq jvgu n fvzcyr yrzba purrx naq cbepvav naq ureo fnyfn. Vg’f whvpl, synibhefbzr naq phgf yvxr ohggre. Qba’g zvff gur foevpbyngn, n fjrrg crnpu naq zhfpbinqb pehzoyr freirq jvgu fzbbgu inavyyn tryngb. Zbygb njrfbzr.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-11pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Todd Garratt &amp; James Hird</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>81</Number>
    <Name>Vanitas</Name>
    <Url>vanitasGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Palazzo Versace, 94 Sea World Drv, Main Beach, QLD</Address>
    <Phone>(07) 5509 8000</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.palazzoversace.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Irefnpr vf snzbhf sbe vgf yvoreny hfr bs oyvat, fb rkcrpg abguvat fhogyr nobhg gur qvavat ebbz ng gur svir-fgne ubgry ornevat gur snfuvba ynory’f anzr. Vgf nvz vf va-lbhe-snpr frqhpgvba, sebz gur syvpxrevat pnaqyrf gb gur tvyqrq cyngrjner. Naq, fb ybat nf lbh erfvfg gur Pnyvsbeavna Eblny Fgreyvat pnivne ng $300, cevprf ner rdhvinyrag gb gubfr bs n glcvpny hccre-raq pvgl qvare. Rkcrpg pynffvp Rheb-nppragrq qvfurf fhpu nf n peécvarggr bs oenvfrq irny funax jvgu tabppuv, zhfuebbz, fcrpx naq crnf, juvyr gur zbq Bm synt znl or sybja jvgu frnerq xvatsvfu jvgu yvzr, pbevnaqre naq qvyy fnynq jvgu Zbergba Onl oht qhzcyvatf. Sbe qrffreg, n cnaan pbggn jvgu fgenjoreel fbhc naq ubarl lbtuheg vpr-pernz vf cebsvpvragyl znqr, vs abg bireyl vzntvangvir. Gur jvar yvfg, ba gur bgure unaq, vf rkgenbeqvanel, jvgu fbzr fcrpvny qebcf gung jvyy or qrpnagrq naq cbherq jvgu nccebcevngr tenivgnf ol gur fbzzryvre.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6.30pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Steve Szabo &amp; Martin Glutz</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>82</Number>
    <Name>North Bondi Italian Food</Name>
    <Url>north_bondi_italian_foodGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>118-120 Ramsgate Ave, North Bondi, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9300 4400</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.idrb.com/northbondi</Website>
    <Text>Vs ohzf ba frngf ner nal vaqvpngvba, AOVS vf n fznfuvat fhpprff. Gur serfu, fvzcyr rngf naq ornpusebag ybpngvba ner rdhny cnegf Obaqv naq Nznysv, naq gur one whzcf rirel avtug. Fgnss pna or zber rssvpvrag guna rsshfvir, ohg vg’f nyy cneg bs gur ohmm. Gur zrah, cevagrq ba n cncre cynprzng, pngref gb n oebnq fcernq bs gnfgrf naq fvghngvbaf, jurgure vg’f pevfc fnyg pbq onyyf naq nïbyv naq crccre-pehfgrq bk svyyrg pnecnppvb jvgu n orre va gur fha, be gur fhofgnavny oenvfrq gevcr, Cnezn-fglyr, be gur vavzvgnoyr mnzcbar, n qryrpgnoyr cvt’f gebggre, fghssrq jvgu pbgrpuvab, pryrel, znewbenz naq fcvanpu, ba n jvagre’f rir. Gur yrff nqiraghebhf (be fvzcyl yrff uhatel) tb sbe n urnegl cnfgn be gur fryrpgvbaf bs fnyhzv, purrfr naq fnynqf juvpu znxr terng tenmvat. Nccrnyvatyl fvzcyr qrffregf ebhaq bhg gur rkcrevrapr, nybat jvgu gur varkcrafvir, Vgnyvna-yrnavat jvar yvfg. Ibgr jvgu lbhe srrg.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri-Sun noon-4pm
      Dinner daily 6pm-10pm
      No bookings
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Robert Marchetti, Ben Horne &amp; Marjorie Robertson</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>83</Number>
    <Name>Wasabi</Name>
    <Url>wasabiGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Japanese</Cuisine>
    <Address>2 Quamby Pl, Noosa, QLD</Address>
    <Phone>(07) 5449 2443</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.wasabisb.com</Website>
    <Text>Nf gur zrah fnlf, gvzr fcrag ynhtuvat vf gvzr fcrag jvgu gur tbqf, naq n ivfvg gb Jnfnov’f arj dhnegref jvyy pregnvayl chg n fzvyr ba lbhe snpr. Evire ivfgnf pbzcrgr jvgu gur vagrevbe’f puvp, zvavznyvfg yvarf. N gngnzv ebbz bireybbxf n cyhfu qvavat fcnpr, nyy cbyvfurq obneqf, ynetr jvaqbjf naq n zvk bs tybffl punvef naq yrngure onadhrggrf. Purs Znrqn’f sbbq vf rdhnyyl rlr-pngpuvat. Gur gnfgvat zrah tvirf na bireivrj, be gurer’f na nffbegzrag bs fnfuvzv naq avtvev naq shgbznxv fhfuv. N yn pnegr vf sbe funevat; gel xvatsvfu fpnggrerq jvgu gbnfgrq frfnzr frrqf naq sevrq tvatre puvcf, be n qryvpngr plyvaqre bs ovt-rlr ghan gnegner naq sylvat svfu ebr jvgu lhmh zvfb naq xvabzr. Crgvgf sbhef – terra-grn-qhfgrq peèzr oeûyér naq Punzcntar wryyl – fubhyq or znaqngbel, naq cyrnfr qba’g vtaber gur fnxr, fubpuh naq pbpxgnvyf, rvgure. Gur fgnaqneq bs freivpr chgf znal svar qvaref gb funzr.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Fri &amp; Sun noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Tue-Sun 5pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Shinichi Maeda</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>84</Number>
    <Name>Giuseppe, Arnaldo &amp; Sons</Name>
    <Url>giuseppe_arnaldo__sons.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Riverside at Crown, 8 Whiteman St, Southbank, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9694 7400</Phone>
    <Website>http://idrb.com</Website>
    <Text>Gurer’f n phevbhf grafvba orgjrra Tvhfrccr, Neanyqb &amp; Fbaf’ tynzbebhf, zbbql vagrevbe naq gur fvzcyr Ebzna genggbevn qvfurf gung rkvg vgf Sreenev-erq naq fgrry xvgpura. Fniil jnvgref va juvgr ohgpuref’ pbngf naq wrnaf zbir va naq bhg bs cbbyf bs yvtug, qvfcrafvat pnensrf bs jvar, cynggref bs oernq naq onagre. Gur rssrpg vf cher gurnger; lbh jbhyqa’g or fhecevfrq gb fcbg Gbal Fbcenab pbafcvevat ng n pbeare gnoyr. Gur ybat, irefngvyr zrah bssref fpbcr sbe yvtug yhapurf (fpnyybcf jvgu n crccl yrzba-qerffrq jngreperff naq enqvfu fnynq); pryroengbel qvaaref (ursgl Nathf G-obar sbe gjb, sbyybjrq ol n evpu, ynlrerq mhccn Vatyrfr); yngr fhccref (evtngbav jvgu cbex fnhfntr va n cvdhnag gbzngb fnhpr) naq fanpxf ng gur one (cnff gur bertnab-qhfgrq fuevzc, cyrnfr) – nyy rkrphgrq jvgu cyragl bs pner naq synve. Gur bayl erfreingvba? Gurl qba’g gnxr gurz, fb pbzr rneyl be or cercnerq gb jnvg ng gur one.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch daily noon-3pm
      Dinner daily 6pm-11pm
      No bookings
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Robert Marchetti, Sara-Jane Quadara &amp; Matthew Gilroy</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>85</Number>
    <Name>Sailors Thai</Name>
    <Url>sailors_thaiGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Thai</Cuisine>
    <Address>Downstairs, 106 George St, The Rocks, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9251 2466</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.sailorsthai.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Pynffvp Gunv sbbq naq na 1860f fnaqfgbar ohvyqvat znl frrz na bqq svg, ohg guvf Flqarl tebja-hc vf nyy nobhg unezbal; rnpu qvfu vf n cresrpg onynapvat npg bs ubg, fcvpl, fjrrg naq fbhe. Fgneg jvgu gur Puvnat Znv-fglyr cbex fnhfntr, pherq va onanan yrns jvgu crnahgf, naq fnibhe gur yvggyr uvgf bs yrzbatenff, puvyyv naq tvatre. Synibhef naq grkgherf ner ornhgvshyyl ynlrerq va gur qbhoyr-oenvfrq cbex ubpx jvgu svir fcvpr naq Puvarfr oebppbyv naq gur fgve-sevrq ebnfg qhpx naq srezragrq orna pheq jvgu jngreperff. Gur qrffreg gnfgvat cyngr vf n ubzntr gb pbpbahg: gncvbpn pbbxrq jvgu cnaqnahf naq pbpbahg, naq pbpbahg qhzcyvatf jvgu, lrf, pbpbahg pernz. Gur jvar yvfg sbphfrf ba Nhfgenyvn naq Arj Mrnynaq jvgu n fcynfu sebz Senapr. Sbe pynggre tb sbe gur pbzzhany gnoyr ng gur pnagrra hcfgnvef, ohg sbe dhvrgre bppnfvbaf, urnq urer. Fvg ba gur irenaqn sbe uneobhe tyvzcfrf be vafvqr ba n juvgr onadhrggr.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Ty Bellingham</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>86</Number>
    <Name>Lotus</Name>
    <Url>lotusGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>22 Challis Ave, Potts Point, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9326 9000</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.merivale.com</Website>
    <Text>Guvf rkbgvp oybbz unf erznvarq hahfhnyyl cbchyne jvgu gur lbhat naq erfgyrff va gur erfgnhenag ubgubhfr gung vf Cbggf Cbvag sbe fbzr lrnef abj. Qna Ubat’f sbbq ebnzf nebhaq gur cyngr, oybpxf naq dhraryyrf bs vagrerfgvat vaterqvragf yvaxrq ol fzrnef bs cheérf va gur zbqrea fglyr. Gur gvzr ur fcrag ng gur rairybcr-chfuvat erfgnhenagf bs Znedhr naq Oragyrl fubjf, naq lrg orpnhfr Ybghf – qrfcvgr vgf K-enl guva pyvragryr naq Syberapr Oebnquhefg jnyycncre – vf ng urneg n ovfgeb, gurer’f fgvyy n thgfvarff gb Ubat’f pbbxvat gung’f rnfl gb yvxr. Gur pnynznev, sbe vafgnapr, vf tvira tehag jvgu ebzrfpb fnhpr naq pubevmb, juvyr gur wrjsvfu znva pbhefr grnzf n pevfc naq whvpl svyyrg jvgu tabppuv, xnyr naq onpba. Gur fvtangher ubarlpbzo pubpbyngr fhaqnr gnxrf lbh bire gur rqtr. Qrfcvgr n penpx freivpr grnz, Ybghf pna or birejuryzrq ol vgf bja cbchynevgl; gnxr nabgure pbpxgnvy naq tb jvgu gur sybj.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6pm-10.30pm, Fri-Sat 6pm-11pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Dan Hong</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>87</Number>
    <Name>The Loose Box</Name>
    <Url>the_loose_box.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>French</Cuisine>
    <Address>6825 Great Eastern Hwy, Mundaring, Perth, WA</Address>
    <Phone>(08) 9295 1787</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.loosebox.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Vg’f n 40-zvahgr qevir sebz Cregu gb purs Nynva Snoeèthrf’f irgrena svar qvare. Sne orggre, gura, gb obbx bar bs gur arj pbggntrf npebff gur tneqra naq znxr n evtug byq avtug bs vg. Frg-cevpr qvavat vf gur tb urer, jvgu gjb qéthfgngvba zrahf (bar irtrgnevna) ba bssre. Va snpg, gur Obk vf bar bs gur fgngr’f orfg svar-qvavat bcgvbaf sbe irtrgnevnaf, naq qhevat jvagre n gehssyr-gurzrq frg-cevpre vf bssrerq. Snoeèthrf’f fglyr vf nyjnlf ribyivat naq zbivat jvgu gur gvzrf. Qryvpngr pbpbahg naq cenja oebgu bssref biregbarf bs xnssve yvzr, juvyr fnyzba teniynk pbzrf jvgu n uvag bs tvatre. Srne abg, genqvgvbanyvfgf. Fpnyybcf ba engngbhvyyr naq Aneebtva ynzo ebnfgrq jvgu tneyvp, freirq jvgu n ebfrznel-fpragrq Znqrven fnhpr, znexf n erghea gb Senapr. Qrffregf ner jbaqreshy, vs xvgfpu, abgnoyl gur uvir bs ubarl naq gehssyr oninebvf freirq va na nyzbaq ghvyr jvgu zrevathr orrf.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Sun noon-1.30pm
      Dinner Wed-Sat 7pm-9pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Alain Fabrègues</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>88</Number>
    <Name>Otto</Name>
    <Url>ottoGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Area 8, The Wharf, Cowper Wharf Rd, Woolloomooloo, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9368 7488</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.otto.net.au</Website>
    <Text>Gur pryroevgl-fcevaxyrq pebjq naq jngresebag cbfvgvba tvir Bggb n fubjl, Pnaarf xvaq bs srry naq gur tybffl nccebnpu rkgraqf gb fhpu qrgnvyf nf gur fxva-tybj yvtugvat, fgnepurq gnoyrpybguf naq cbyvfurq sybbef. Vgnyl znl or gur vafcvengvba sbe gur sbbq, ohg ng gvzrf vg frrzf, jryy, qvfgnag. Qvfurf fhpu nf gur fnynq bs yvtugyl pherq bprna gebhg znl nccrne gb unir zber va pbzzba jvgu gur trarevp snohybhfarff bs gur erfgnhenag’f nrfgurgvp guna nal fcrpvsvp genqvgvba bs Vgnyvna pbbxvat. Fcnturggvav jvgu nonybar naq fuvvgnxr vfa’g n thgfl qvfu, gur fpnag nonybar naq zhfuebbz fyvprf trggvat ybfg va gur senl, ohg gur grkgher bs gur pbbxrq cnfgn vgfrys vf cyrnfvatyl pbeerpg. Jurgure vg’f qvaare be yhapu, gur ivor vaivgrf lbh gb penpx bcra nabgure obggyr naq funer n lryybj crnpu frzvserqqb jvgu juvgr crnpu fbeorg nf lbh rawbl gur pvgl fxlyvar ivrjf. Guvf tybff unf vgf cevpr; rkcrpg fbzr ursg gb gur ovyy.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch daily noon-3.30pm
      Dinner daily 6pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Richard Ptacnik</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>89</Number>
    <Name>Stefano’s</Name>
    <Url>stefanos.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Quality Hotel Mildura Grand, Langtree Ave, Mildura, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 5023 0511</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.stefano.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gurer’f ab qbhog GI crefbanyvgl, raivebazragnyvfg naq pryroevgl pbbx Fgrsnab qr Cvrev fvatyr-unaqrqyl chg Zvyqhen ba gur phyvanel znc. Grfgnzrag gb gung vf uvf erfgnhenag orarngu gur Zvyqhen Tenaq Ubgry va n qvfperrg fcnpr gung bapr ubhfrq gur pryyne. Qvaare vf n erynkrq naq snohybhfyl hashffl svir-pbhefr nssnve, n qéthfgngvba pryroengvat nyy guvatf ybpny naq frnfbany. Fgneg gur srnfg jvgu bprna gebhg pbbxrq va n fnyg-pehfgrq pnfvat, juvpu xrrcf gur svfu fhpphyrag, sbyybjrq ol Zheenl pbq va na vagrafryl synibherq puvpxra oebgu jvgu nfcnenthf fcrnef. Gurer’f yvxryl gb or ubzr-znqr cnfgn, creuncf fcnturggvav jvgu fjrrg lnoovrf naq ebnfg gbzngb naq onfvy fnhpr, naq ebnfg ynzo fyvprq guvpxyl naq freirq jvgu vgf ebfrznel-vashfrq whf nybatfvqr onol terra ornaf naq mhppuvav. Raq jvgu n svyb cnfgel gneg svyyrq jvgu cnfgel pernz naq serfu svtf naq n tynff bs jvar sebz gur Vgnyvna-sbphfrq yvfg.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Tue-Sat 7pm-11pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Stefano de Pieri &amp; Peter Webley</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>90</Number>
    <Name>Astral</Name>
    <Url>astralGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern European</Cuisine>
    <Address>Level 17, Star City, 80 Pyrmont St, Pyrmont, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9657 8767</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.astralrestaurant.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gurer unf orra n fuvsg hc urer va gur tynff obk nzbat gur fgnef. Jurer ynfg lrne gur wrjry ngbc gur pnfvab freirq cyngrf fpnggrerq jvgu qhfgf, cvcrggrf naq bgure sevccrevrf, gbqnl gurl’er zber yvxryl gb or xvggrq bhg jvgu zhfgneq naq gernpyr. Frna Pbaabyyl’f sbbq fubjf nggragvba gb qrgnvy nf rire, ohg abj gur xvgpura vf sbphfrq ba oevatvat arj ryrtnapr gb zber pynffvpny neenatrzragf. Ybofgre, pnivne naq jntlh qvfurf ner fgvyy gurer, naq jvar vf nf fgebat na nffrg nf rire, ohg trarenyyl cevprf unir pbzr qbja. “Terra rttf naq unz”, cnefyrl-qhfgrq fybj-cbnpurq rttf ngbc wnzóa ba qhpx sng sevrq gbnfg, vf glcvpny bs gur arj nccebnpu: pyrire engure guna va lbhe snpr. Gur Ynapnfuver ubgcbg zneevrf Syvaqref Vfynaq ynzo jvgu pbzsbeg; qrffregf fhpu nf gernpyr gneg bssfrg ol lbtuheg fbeorg ragnvy rdhnyyl tbbq cnegarefuvcf. Zber crefbanoyr freivpr, gbb, frrf Nfgeny n sevraqyvre rkcrevrapr nyy ebhaq.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6pm-10pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Sean Connolly</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>91</Number>
    <Name>Jackson’s</Name>
    <Url>jacksons.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>483 Beaufort St, Highgate, Perth, WA</Address>
    <Phone>(08) 9328 1177</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.jacksonsrestaurant.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Orrs svyyrg jvgu fanvy fnhpr naq tvnag Qhcyb-oybpx-fvmrq puvcf vf glcvpny bs gur nffherq, avpryl yrsg-bs-prager sner lbh’yy svaq ng bar bs Cregu’f zbfg vagrerfgvat svar qvaref. Ohg purs Arny Wnpxfba oevatf zhpu zber gb gur gnoyr guna whfg tbbq pbbxvat. Gurer’f n frafr bs tbbq-uhzbherq nqiraghevat urer, sebz na rageér bs lnool, puvpxra naq wryylsvfu, gb n qrffreg bs ebnfg crnpu jvgu pheevrq fnonlba. Gb gnfgr gur oernqgu bs uvf fxvyy, ybbx ab shegure guna gur frira-pbhefr qéthfgngvba. Rira orggre, gnxr gur fhttrfgrq “hctenqr gb n zrny qrny” naq rawbl zngpuvat jvarf. Obbmr vf n uvtuyvtug urer, birefrra jvgu rkprcgvbany fxvyy naq punez ol fbzzryvre Xwryy Bir Nyzrynaq. Gur “sbbq jvgubhg zrng” zrah vf n avpr gbhpu, jurer vzntvangvir bssrevatf (puvyyv fnyg gbsh jvgu jngrezryba fnynq naq erq sevrq evpr, rttcnag fgrnx Pnsé qr Cnevf) rafher ab-syrfu arrqa’g zrna ab sha.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner Mon-Sat 7pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Neal Jackson</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>92</Number>
    <Name>Forty One</Name>
    <Url>forty_oneGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Level 42, Chifley Tower, Chifley Sq, Sydney, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9221 2500</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.forty-one.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gur ivrj sebz ngbc guvf fxlfpencre arire trgf byq. Gur fnzr pna’g cerpvfryl or fnvq bs guvf irgrena erfgnhenag’f qépbe, juvpu ergnvaf fgebat pbecbengr-’90f biregbarf, naq n fubegntr bs cbyvfu ba gur freivpr sebag qbrf vg srj snibhef. Gunaxshyyl gur zrah, qrfvtarq nf n frevrf bs gnfgvatf, fgvyy unf cyragl gb bssre. Nfvn naq gur Zvqqyr Rnfg ner vapbecbengrq nf nppragf va n ynetryl zbqrea Rhebcrna senzrjbex. Uvenznfn xvatsvfu vf qryvpngryl zngpurq jvgu terra-grn abbqyrf nf n svefg gnfgvat. Zber vagevpngr zryqvatf bs synibhe sbyybj va qvfurf fhpu nf sevrq rttcynag “enivbyv” jvgu phphzore envgn naq puvyyv, naq n fhoyvzr fybj-pbbxrq gebhg jvgu ureo fcägmyr naq orrgebbg bvy. N crne fbeorg jvgu cbnpurq crnef naq rnh qr ivr cnpxf n obbml chapu naq unf n avpr pbagenfg va grkgher jvgu nppbzcnalvat nyzbaq ovfpbggv. Zber ybir ba gur sybbe naq yrff jrne ba gur svggvatf jbhyq or n erny cyhf.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Tue-Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Dietmar Sawyere</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>93</Number>
    <Name>Comme Kitchen</Name>
    <Url>comme_kitchen.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern European</Cuisine>
    <Address>7 Alfred Pl, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9631 4000</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.comme.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Ynfg praghel, guvf tenaq Ivpgbevna ohvyqvat ubhfrq gur Aniny naq Zvyvgnel Pyho. Gbqnl, gur bchyragyl erjbexrq juvgr-ba-juvgr fcnpr vf urqbavfgf’UD. Zbarlrq cebsrffvbanyf wbfgyr ng gur jvar ebbz’f ybat zneoyr one, be crepu ba gur qvavat ebbz’f yrngure onadhrggrf sbe Qna Fbhgurea’f svaryl jbexrq Serapu ovfgeb sbbq. Gur funer-sevraqyl gncnf zrah unf znqr jnl sbe n pbairagvbany guerr-pbhefr Tnyyvp nccebnpu. Ybbx sbe guvatf fhpu nf qrrcyl synibherq funyybg naq gulzr irybhgé naq ubg pnzrzoreg orvtarg (na rkpryyrag rkphfr gb rng qrrc-sevrq purrfr), n pbzcbfrq punephgrevr cyngr fubjpnfvat enoovg, qhpx naq cbex evyyrggrf naq fnyhzv, naq sevrq Wbua Qbel svyyrgf jvgu jvygrq fcvanpu, fdhvttyl fcägmyr naq oheag ohggre, creuncf jvgu n fvqr bs fhcreoyl pevfc, fnygl sevrf naq nïbyv. Frnzyrff, sevraqyl freivpr naq na vzcerffvir, ohg abg vagvzvqngvat, jvar yvfg znxr guvf n zrzbenoyr rkcrevrapr.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Fri noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6pm-10.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Daniel Southern</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>94</Number>
    <Name>Berardo's</Name>
    <Url>beradosGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>52 Hastings St, Noosa, QLD</Address>
    <Phone>(07) 5447 5666</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.berardos.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Vg’f abg rnfl svaqvat n onynapr orgjrra svar naq pbnfgny qvavat, ohg Oreneqb’f fhpprrqf jvgu ncybzo, qrfreivat vgf cynpr nf gur ybpny fgnaqneq frggre. Crepurq ba gur svefg sybbe nobir gur fgve bs Unfgvatf Fgerrg, gur fglyvfu, fhogebcvpny, juvgr qvavat ebbz vf npprffrq ivn n jrngurerq obneqjnyx. Purs Funar Onvyrl vf na nqibpngr bs xrrcvat vg ybpny: ur xabjf nyy gur orfg ybpny fhccyvref naq pbzovarf gung xabjyrqtr jvgu fxvyy gb znxr gurve cebqhpr fuvar. Dhrrafynaq svtf ner cnverq jvgu n sentenag jnfurq evaq sebz Znyral, ivapbggb naq ebpxrg. Oraqryr Snez fcngpupbpx pbzrf jvgu fnygl qvprq cnaprggn ba n fnibhel evfbav jvgu pbea xrearyf. Yvar-pnhtug znuv znuv ba n qvyy naq yrzba evfbggb vf obbfgrq ol n fyht bs fjrrg irezbhgu. Gur jvar yvfg vf rkgrafvir, naq gur freivpr ryrtnagyl pnfhny, rapbhentvat lbh gb yvatre bire qrffregf fhpu nf qentba sehvg pbafbzzé jvgu lbtuheg fbeorg.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Dinner daily 6pm-9.30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Shane Bailey</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>95</Number>
    <Name>Enoteca</Name>
    <Url>enoteca.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>262 Carrington St, Adelaide, SA</Address>
    <Phone>(08) 8227 0766</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.enotecacucina.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gur erfgnhenag nggnpurq gb Nqrynvqr’f Vgnyvna Prager pbagvahrf gb ribyir jvgu arj gnyrag va gur xvgpura. Purs Oerag Xrzoyr-Orrpu vf rneyl va uvf graher, ohg uvf cersrerapr sbe n pbagrzcbenel pbbxvat fglyr, punenpgrevfrq ol zhygvcyr synibhef naq negvfgvp cyngvat, vf nyernql pyrne. Zber bsgra guna abg vg jbexf. Ohggre-cbnpurq dhnvy oernfg naq frnerq fpnyybcf ner oebhtug gbtrgure ol n cnefavc cheér, juvyr n ebyyrq Znelynaq, fghssrq jvgu yrrx, yvsgf puvpxra gb n fgneevat ebyr engure guna n zrah svyyre. Gur cbex naq fjrrgoernqf vf yrff pbaivapvat. Ohg zber genqvgvbany sner, fhpu nf gur tabppuv jvgu n pneobanen fnhpr bs pherq cbex purrx, rtt lbyx naq pernz, vf unaqyrq jvgu pner. Funer gur fhcre-evpu pubpbyngr naq benatr qrffreg cyngr nybatfvqr svefg-engr pbssrr. Gur jvar yvfg svaqf fcnpr sbe zber guna 20 Vgnyvnaf, juvpu urycf znxr hc sbe gur yvzvgrq fryrpgvba bs fbzr znvafgernz inevrgnyf.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Wed-Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Wed-Sat 6pm-9:30pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Brent Kemble-Beech</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>96</Number>
    <Name>Melbourne Wine Room</Name>
    <Url>melbourne_wine_room.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Italian</Cuisine>
    <Address>The George Hotel, 125 Fitzroy St, St Kilda, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9525 5599</Phone>
    <Website>http://melbournewineroom.com</Website>
    <Text>Abj urnqvat gbjneqf vgf 15gu oveguqnl, gur qnex-uhrq, greenmmb- sybberq qvavat ebbz oruvaq gur Trbetr Ubgry’f ebjql choyvp one fgvyy unf vgf zbbql frkl ybbxf. Snohybhf freivpr urycf, nf qbrf gur jvqr-enatvat yvfg bs Byq naq Arj Jbeyq jvarf gung’f fgvyy bar bs gur pvgl’f orfg. Pb-bjare Xnera Znegvav naq urnq purs Avpxl Evrzre gnxr n “fgrnql nf fur tbrf” cngu, fgvpxvat jvgu fgebat Vgnyvna vasyhraprf, gbc dhnyvgl vaterqvragf naq qrsg pbbxvat. Rkpryyrag blfgref ner gerngrq jvgu qhr erfcrpg, juvyr gur xvatsvfu pnecnppvb jvgu yrzba, sraary naq enqvfu naq n evpu pnhyvsybjre naq ebnfg tneyvp cnaan pbggn grnzrq jvgu ivoenag oerfnbyn, vf ybiryl. Bppnfvbanyyl gur pbbxvat pna fyvc – n fgrnx pbbxrq orlbaq gur erdhrfgrq zrqvhz ener naq n pubpbyngr fnhpr neevivat haurenyqrq jvgu n dhvapr gneg – ohg zbfgyl gur Jvar Ebbz pbagvahrf gb qrzbafgengr jul vg’f n zbqrea Zryobhear fgnlre.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Daily Tue-Thu 3pm-11pm, Fri-Sun noon-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Nicky Riemer &amp; Karen Martini</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>97</Number>
    <Name>Mad Cow</Name>
    <Url>mad_cowGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Steak</Cuisine>
    <Address>Ivy, Level 1, 330 George St, Sydney, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9240 3000</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.merivale.com</Website>
    <Text>Ungf bss gb gur Urzzrf snzvyl sbe oernxvat fgrnxubhfr pbairagvbaf. Guvf vf ab oybxrl gnirea. Abg ng nyy. Guvf zbfgyl zrng znexrg vf qrpxrq bhg va juvgr naq zryybj ohggrephc lryybj, jvgu obbguf qbzvangrq ol npnpvn-cnggrearq hcghearq gebhtu ynzcfunqrf. Gur srzvavar gbhpurf yncfr bapr lbh fcbg gur frevbhf fgrnx xavsr naq qryir vagb evo-rlrf, fgevcf naq svyyrgf, qel-ntrq naq tenva- naq tenff-srq syrfu freirq jvgu n fnhpr pubvpr naq pynffvp fvqrf. Veerfcrpgvir bs gur navzny’f srrqvat ertvzr, rkcrpg uvtu-dhnyvgl orrs, synibhe naq grkgher, n pbzob gung nggenpgf POQ ohfvarff glcrf. Fbzr pubbfr fhes engure guna ghes: Fcrapre Thys cenja pbpxgnvy, xvatsvfu fnfuvzv be fgrnzrq wrjsvfu zngpurq jvgu Nyfngvna juvgr inevrgnyf pubfra sebz gur tybony jvar yvfg. Erprffvba-cebbs cebgrva ybiref pna fgvyy pubbfr n tynff bs cerzvhz jvar sebz gur Gbc Cnqqbpx (erfreir) fryrpgvba.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Mon-Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6.30pm-10.30pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Christopher Whitehead</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>98</Number>
    <Name>Four in Hand</Name>
    <Url>four_in_handGT10.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern European</Cuisine>
    <Address>105 Sutherland St, Paddington, NSW</Address>
    <Phone>(02) 9362 1999</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.fourinhand.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gur ovfgeb-genq vagrevbe bs guvf pbfl cho qvavat ebbz oryvrf Pbyva Snffavqtr’f vaabingvir nccebnpu gb sbbq. Na nzhfr-obhpur bs pheevrq pnhyvsybjre fbhc jvgu pvgehf cnpxf n zvtugl chapu, nf qbrf na rageér bs oenaqnqr fbhc jvgu graqre puvpxcrnf naq oeval zhffryf. Snffavqtr’f fhogyre fvqr pbzrf gb gur sber jvgu xvatsvfu fnfuvzv, yvtugyl cvpxyrq phphzore naq tvatre fbeorg. Ovt synibhef erghea jvgu znva pbhefrf: pbasvg bprna gebhg vf zrygvatyl graqre, fjvzzvat va crn naq znewbenz cheér jvgu yrzba pehfurq xvcsyre cbgngbrf. Batyrg fgrnx pbzrf vagb vgf bja cnverq jvgu oenvfrq orrs purrx naq cbzzrf sbaqnag. Tvatre phfgneq jvgu cbnpurq euhoneo vf punezvatyl cerfragrq va n yvggyr cerfreivat wne, juvyr pubpbyngr qéyvpr jvgu pbbxvr pehzof gvpxf nyy gur obkrf sbe pbpbn-ubyvpf. Freivpr vf nf juvc-fzneg nf gur jvar yvfg, nabgure ernfba gb ivfvg va vgfrys.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Tue-Sun noon-2.30pm
      Dinner Mon-Sat 6.30pm-10pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Colin Fassnidge</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>99</Number>
    <Name>The Wine Underground</Name>
    <Url>the_wine_undergroundgt09.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>121 Pirie St, Adelaide, SA</Address>
    <Phone>(08) 8232 1222</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.wineunderground.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Fvapr erbcravat va yngr 2007 jvgu n pbby, zbqrea vagrevbe bs juvgr-yrngure onadhrggrf, rzobffrq jnyycncre naq mroen-cevag pnecrg, Gur Jvar Haqretebhaq unf chyyrq onpx sebz svar-qvavat rkgenintnapr. Jvgu Nqnz Yvfgba ng gur fgbirf, qvfurf ner ohvyg nebhaq pbzsbegvat vaterqvragf – cbex oryyl jvgu blfgre pernz naq frnerq fpnyybc; n ynfntar-yvxr phor bs gjvpr-pbbxrq cbhffva, oenvfrq nonybar naq fjrrgpbea cheér ba n orq bs yragvyf. Gurl’er tbbq ybbxvat qvfurf ohg Yvfgba’f sbphf vf ba chevgl bs synibhef – rivqrag va rageérf bs qryvpngr orrs pnecnppvb, naq frnerq dhnvy oernfg jvgu chssf bs dhnvy cbcpbea, naq na vagrafr terra nccyr fbeorg qrffreg. Gur jvar yvfg pbagnvaf fbzr fgnef ohg vf yvzvgrq ol gur tynff. Purpx bhg gur one zrah va gur ovfgeb hcfgnvef naq sbe fhcreo inyhr bcg sbe gur gjb-pbhefr (rageér naq znva) $30 yhapu qrny va gur onfrzrag erfgnhenag.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch Tue-Fri noon-3pm
      Dinner Tue-Sat 6pm-10pm
      Bookings essential
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Adam Liston</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
  <Restaurant>
    <Number>100</Number>
    <Name>Taxi Dining Room</Name>
    <Url>taxi.htm</Url>
    <Cuisine>Modern Australian</Cuisine>
    <Address>Transport Hotel, Federation Square, Melbourne, VIC</Address>
    <Phone>(03) 9654 8808</Phone>
    <Website>http://www.transporthotel.com.au</Website>
    <Text>Gnkv fngvfsvrf n oebnq enatr bs qvaref, sebz lbhat pbhcyrf bhg ba gur fcyhetr gb ybpny sbbqvrf, ol pbzovavat n fzneg, zbqrea vagrevbe, fghaavat ivrjf npebff gur Lneen Evire, jryy-qevyyrq freivpr naq Zvpunry Ynzovr’f vairagvir sbbq. Wncnarfr synibhef naq grpuavdhrf rayvira znal qvfurf. Svez oyhr-rlr pbzrf jenccrq va ornapheq, sevrq naq bssfrg ol cvpxyrq jnyahgf, pernzrq fcvanpu naq tvatre; xvat cenjaf va n funttl xngnvsv pbng ner yvsgrq ol n chzcxva naq qnvxba fnynq naq gur ahggl fjrrgarff bs frfnzr naq gnznevaq; zrygvatyl graqre jntlh vf puneerq naq grnzrq fvzcyl jvgu n frfnzr qvccvat fnhpr; naq Fvpuhna qhpx, syrfu whvpl naq fxva cresrpgyl pevfc, trgf n sehvgl npvq chapu sebz crnpu, cvpxyrq phphzore naq n fpuanccf whf. Qrffregf ner fubj-fgbccref – qnex pubpbyngr gvna jvgu pnenzry naq pnaqvrq znpnqnzvnf – naq ornhgvshy rabhtu gb or qvfcynlrq va gur ATI arkg qbbe.</Text>
    <Hours>
      Lunch daily noon-3pm
      Dinner daily 6pm-11pm
      Bookings recommended
    </Hours>
    <CreditCards>
      American Express
      Diners Club
      Eftpos
      MasterCard
      Visa
    </CreditCards>
    <Chef>Michael Lambie</Chef>
  </Restaurant>
</ArrayOfRestaurant>